t=B-PER+w=EU -1
ti=B-PER+ti-1=<START> -1
Oi=eu+t=B-PER -1
p=NNP+t=B-PER -2
t=B-PER+w=rejects -1
ti=B-PER+ti-1=B-PER -8
Oi=rejects+t=B-PER -1
p=VBZ+t=B-PER -1
t=B-PER+w=German -1
Oi=german+t=B-PER -1
p=JJ+t=B-PER -2
t=B-PER+w=call -1
Oi=call+t=B-PER -1
p=NN+t=B-PER -2
t=B-PER+w=to -1
Oi=to+t=B-PER -1
p=TO+t=B-PER -1
t=B-PER+w=boycott -1
Oi=boycott+t=B-PER -1
p=VB+t=B-PER -1
t=B-PER+w=British -1
Oi=british+t=B-PER -1
t=B-PER+w=lamb -1
Oi=lamb+t=B-PER -1
t=B-PER+w=. -1
Oi=.+t=B-PER -1
p=.+t=B-PER -1
t=<STOP>+w=<STOP> 0
ti=<STOP>+ti-1=B-PER -1
Oi=<stop>+t=<STOP> 0
p=<STOP>+t=<STOP> 0
t=I-ORG+w=EU 9
ti=I-ORG+ti-1=<START> -3
Oi=eu+t=I-ORG 9
p=NNP+t=I-ORG 1
t=O+w=rejects 1
ti=O+ti-1=I-ORG 10
Oi=rejects+t=O 1
p=VBZ+t=O 5
t=I-MISC+w=German 9
ti=I-MISC+ti-1=O 2
Oi=german+t=I-MISC 14
p=JJ+t=I-MISC 4
t=O+w=call 2
ti=O+ti-1=I-MISC 12
Oi=call+t=O 2
p=NN+t=O 4
t=O+w=to 10
ti=O+ti-1=O 13
Oi=to+t=O 13
p=TO+t=O -1
t=O+w=boycott 1
Oi=boycott+t=O 1
p=VB+t=O 2
t=I-MISC+w=British 8
Oi=british+t=I-MISC 8
t=O+w=lamb 1
Oi=lamb+t=O 1
t=O+w=. 3
Oi=.+t=O 3
p=.+t=O 1
ti=<STOP>+ti-1=O 72
t=I-ORG+w=Peter -4
Oi=peter+t=I-ORG -4
t=I-ORG+w=Blackburn 7
ti=I-ORG+ti-1=I-ORG 10
Oi=blackburn+t=I-ORG 9
ti=<STOP>+ti-1=I-ORG -54
t=I-PER+w=Peter 6
ti=I-PER+ti-1=<START> 2
Oi=peter+t=I-PER 6
p=NNP+t=I-PER 6
t=I-PER+w=Blackburn 0
ti=I-PER+ti-1=I-PER 12
Oi=blackburn+t=I-PER -2
ti=<STOP>+ti-1=I-PER -1
t=I-PER+w=BRUSSELS -2
Oi=brussels+t=I-PER -4
t=I-PER+w=1996-08-22 -1
Oi=1996-08-22+t=I-PER -1
p=CD+t=I-PER -1
t=I-LOC+w=BRUSSELS 5
ti=I-LOC+ti-1=<START> 3
Oi=brussels+t=I-LOC 7
p=NNP+t=I-LOC 4
t=O+w=1996-08-22 2
ti=O+ti-1=I-LOC 9
Oi=1996-08-22+t=O 2
p=CD+t=O 6
t=O+w=The 1
ti=O+ti-1=<START> 13
Oi=the+t=O 5
p=DT+t=O -4
t=O+w=European -7
Oi=european+t=O -10
p=NNP+t=O -10
t=O+w=Commission -8
Oi=commission+t=O -4
t=O+w=said 7
Oi=said+t=O -1
p=VBD+t=O 8
t=O+w=on 1
Oi=on+t=O 9
p=IN+t=O 4
t=O+w=Thursday 8
Oi=thursday+t=O 11
t=O+w=it 3
Oi=it+t=O 3
p=PRP+t=O 4
t=O+w=disagreed 0
Oi=disagreed+t=O 0
t=O+w=with 5
Oi=with+t=O 5
t=O+w=advice 1
Oi=advice+t=O 1
t=O+w=consumers 0
Oi=consumers+t=O 0
p=NNS+t=O 2
t=O+w=shun 0
Oi=shun+t=O 0
t=O+w=until 2
Oi=until+t=O 2
t=O+w=scientists 0
Oi=scientists+t=O 0
t=O+w=determine 1
Oi=determine+t=O 1
p=VBP+t=O 3
t=O+w=whether 1
Oi=whether+t=O 1
t=I-MISC+w=mad -2
Oi=mad+t=I-MISC -2
t=O+w=cow 1
Oi=cow+t=O 1
t=O+w=disease 2
Oi=disease+t=O 1
t=O+w=can 0
Oi=can+t=O 3
p=MD+t=O 6
t=O+w=be 4
Oi=be+t=O 4
t=O+w=transmitted 1
Oi=transmitted+t=O 1
p=VBN+t=O 4
t=O+w=sheep 0
Oi=sheep+t=O 4
t=I-ORG+w=European 7
ti=I-ORG+ti-1=O 2
Oi=european+t=I-ORG 4
t=I-ORG+w=Commission 9
Oi=commission+t=I-ORG 5
t=O+w=mad 2
Oi=mad+t=O 2
p=JJ+t=O -1
t=I-LOC+w=Germany 6
Oi=germany+t=I-LOC 8
t=O+w='s 5
Oi='s+t=O 3
p=POS+t=O 2
t=O+w=representative 1
Oi=representative+t=O 1
t=O+w=the 3
t=I-ORG+w=Union 5
Oi=union+t=I-ORG 8
t=O+w=veterinary 3
Oi=veterinary+t=O 3
t=O+w=committee 3
Oi=committee+t=O 1
t=I-ORG+w=Werner -3
Oi=werner+t=I-ORG -3
t=I-ORG+w=Zwingmann -2
Oi=zwingmann+t=I-ORG -2
t=I-ORG+w=Wednesday 4
Oi=wednesday+t=I-ORG 0
t=O+w=should 1
Oi=should+t=O 1
t=O+w=buy 1
Oi=buy+t=O 1
t=O+w=sheepmeat 0
Oi=sheepmeat+t=O 0
t=O+w=from 4
Oi=from+t=O 8
t=O+w=countries 3
Oi=countries+t=O 0
t=O+w=other 4
Oi=other+t=O 4
t=O+w=than 0
Oi=than+t=O 0
t=I-ORG+w=Britain -1
Oi=britain+t=I-ORG -2
t=O+w=scientific 2
Oi=scientific+t=O 2
t=O+w=was 6
Oi=was+t=O 6
t=O+w=clearer 0
Oi=clearer+t=O 0
p=JJR+t=O -2
t=I-PER+w=Werner 3
ti=I-PER+ti-1=O 1
Oi=werner+t=I-PER 3
t=I-PER+w=Zwingmann 3
Oi=zwingmann+t=I-PER 3
ti=O+ti-1=I-PER 10
t=O+w=Wednesday 7
Oi=wednesday+t=O 11
t=I-LOC+w=Britain 8
ti=I-LOC+ti-1=O 4
Oi=britain+t=I-LOC 10
t=O+w=" 6
Oi="+t=O 6
p="+t=O 6
t=O+w=We 0
Oi=we+t=O 2
t=O+w=do 3
Oi=do+t=O 3
t=O+w=n't 1
Oi=n't+t=O 1
p=RB+t=O 1
t=O+w=support 2
Oi=support+t=O 1
t=O+w=any 3
Oi=any+t=O 3
t=O+w=such 2
Oi=such+t=O 2
t=O+w=recommendation 0
Oi=recommendation+t=O 0
t=O+w=because 3
Oi=because+t=O 3
t=O+w=we 2
t=O+w=see 2
Oi=see+t=O 2
t=O+w=grounds 0
Oi=grounds+t=O 0
t=O+w=for 0
Oi=for+t=O 3
t=O+w=, 5
Oi=,+t=O 5
p=,+t=O 6
t=I-PER+w=Commission -3
Oi=commission+t=I-PER -3
t=O+w=chief 2
Oi=chief+t=O 8
t=O+w=spokesman 4
Oi=spokesman+t=O 8
t=O+w=Nikolaus -1
Oi=nikolaus+t=O -1
t=O+w=van 2
Oi=van+t=O 3
t=O+w=der -3
Oi=der+t=O -3
p=FW+t=O -2
t=O+w=Pas -1
Oi=pas+t=O -1
t=O+w=told 4
Oi=told+t=O 4
t=O+w=a 14
Oi=a+t=O 13
t=O+w=news 9
Oi=news+t=O -3
t=O+w=briefing 0
Oi=briefing+t=O 0
t=I-PER+w=Nikolaus 1
Oi=nikolaus+t=I-PER 1
t=I-PER+w=van 2
Oi=van+t=I-PER 0
t=I-PER+w=der 5
Oi=der+t=I-PER 4
p=FW+t=I-PER 1
t=I-PER+w=Pas 1
Oi=pas+t=I-PER 1
t=I-PER+w=He -1
Oi=he+t=I-PER -2
p=PRP+t=I-PER -5
t=I-PER+w=said -4
Oi=said+t=I-PER 4
p=VBD+t=I-PER 1
t=I-PER+w=further -2
Oi=further+t=I-PER -2
p=JJ+t=I-PER -1
t=I-PER+w=scientific -1
Oi=scientific+t=I-PER -1
t=I-PER+w=study -1
Oi=study+t=I-PER -1
p=NN+t=I-PER 3
t=I-PER+w=was -3
Oi=was+t=I-PER -3
t=I-PER+w=required -1
Oi=required+t=I-PER -1
p=VBN+t=I-PER -2
t=I-PER+w=and -3
Oi=and+t=I-PER -3
p=CC+t=I-PER -5
t=I-PER+w=if -2
Oi=if+t=I-PER -2
p=IN+t=I-PER -1
t=I-PER+w=it -2
Oi=it+t=I-PER -2
t=I-PER+w=found -2
Oi=found+t=I-PER -2
t=I-PER+w=that -1
Oi=that+t=I-PER -1
t=I-PER+w=action -1
Oi=action+t=I-PER -1
t=I-PER+w=needed -1
Oi=needed+t=I-PER -1
t=I-PER+w=should -1
Oi=should+t=I-PER -1
p=MD+t=I-PER 1
t=I-PER+w=be -3
Oi=be+t=I-PER -3
p=VB+t=I-PER 0
t=I-PER+w=taken -1
Oi=taken+t=I-PER -1
t=I-PER+w=by -1
Oi=by+t=I-PER -2
t=I-PER+w=the 2
Oi=the+t=I-PER 0
p=DT+t=I-PER -1
t=I-PER+w=European -2
Oi=european+t=I-PER -3
t=I-PER+w=Union -3
Oi=union+t=I-PER -3
t=I-PER+w=. -1
Oi=.+t=I-PER -1
p=.+t=I-PER -1
t=O+w=He 2
Oi=he+t=O 8
t=O+w=further 4
Oi=further+t=O 5
t=O+w=study 1
Oi=study+t=O 1
t=O+w=required 1
Oi=required+t=O 1
t=O+w=and 3
Oi=and+t=O 6
p=CC+t=O 7
t=O+w=if 3
Oi=if+t=O 3
t=O+w=found 2
Oi=found+t=O 2
t=O+w=that 7
Oi=that+t=O 7
t=O+w=action 2
Oi=action+t=O 0
t=O+w=needed 1
Oi=needed+t=O 1
t=O+w=taken 1
Oi=taken+t=O 1
t=O+w=by 2
Oi=by+t=O 8
t=O+w=proposal 0
Oi=proposal+t=O 0
t=O+w=last 5
Oi=last+t=O 10
t=O+w=month 1
Oi=month+t=O 5
t=O+w=EU -3
Oi=eu+t=O -3
t=O+w=Farm 7
Oi=farm+t=O 3
t=O+w=Commissioner 7
Oi=commissioner+t=O 7
t=O+w=Franz -1
Oi=franz+t=O -1
t=O+w=Fischler -3
Oi=fischler+t=O -3
t=O+w=ban 2
Oi=ban+t=O 3
t=O+w=brains 0
Oi=brains+t=O 0
t=O+w=spleens 0
Oi=spleens+t=O 0
t=O+w=spinal 1
Oi=spinal+t=O 1
t=O+w=cords 0
Oi=cords+t=O 0
t=O+w=human 4
Oi=human+t=O 4
t=O+w=animal 1
Oi=animal+t=O 1
t=O+w=food 2
Oi=food+t=O -2
t=O+w=chains 0
Oi=chains+t=O 0
t=O+w=highly 0
Oi=highly+t=O 0
t=O+w=specific 2
Oi=specific+t=O 2
t=O+w=precautionary 0
Oi=precautionary+t=O 0
t=O+w=move 2
Oi=move+t=O 2
t=O+w=protect 1
Oi=protect+t=O 1
t=O+w=health 1
Oi=health+t=O 3
t=I-PER+w=Franz 2
Oi=franz+t=I-PER 2
t=I-PER+w=Fischler 5
Oi=fischler+t=I-PER 5
t=O+w=proposed 1
Oi=proposed+t=O 1
t=O+w=EU-wide -2
Oi=eu-wide+t=O -2
t=O+w=measures 2
Oi=measures+t=O 2
t=O+w=after 3
Oi=after+t=O 11
t=O+w=reports 2
Oi=reports+t=O 2
t=O+w=Britain -5
Oi=britain+t=O -5
t=O+w=France -5
Oi=france+t=O -8
p=WDT+t=O -8
t=O+w=under 2
Oi=under+t=O 2
t=O+w=laboratory 0
Oi=laboratory+t=O 0
t=O+w=conditions 1
Oi=conditions+t=O 4
t=O+w=could 2
Oi=could+t=O 2
t=O+w=contract 0
Oi=contract+t=O 6
t=O+w=Bovine -1
Oi=bovine+t=O 1
t=O+w=Spongiform -1
Oi=spongiform+t=O 0
t=O+w=Encephalopathy -1
Oi=encephalopathy+t=O 0
t=O+w=( 5
Oi=(+t=O 5
p=(+t=O 6
t=O+w=BSE -3
Oi=bse+t=O -3
t=O+w=) 3
Oi=)+t=O 3
p=)+t=O 4
t=O+w=-- 2
Oi=--+t=O 2
p=:+t=O 10
p=JJR+t=I-PER 3
t=I-MISC+w=EU-wide 4
Oi=eu-wide+t=I-MISC 4
p=NNP+t=I-MISC 4
t=I-LOC+w=France 5
Oi=france+t=I-LOC 8
t=I-MISC+w=Bovine 5
Oi=bovine+t=I-MISC 3
t=I-MISC+w=Spongiform 5
ti=I-MISC+ti-1=I-MISC 11
Oi=spongiform+t=I-MISC 4
t=I-MISC+w=Encephalopathy 5
Oi=encephalopathy+t=I-MISC 4
t=I-MISC+w=BSE 6
Oi=bse+t=I-MISC 6
t=O+w=But 2
Oi=but+t=O 7
t=O+w=agreed 2
Oi=agreed+t=O 2
t=I-MISC+w=to -2
Oi=to+t=I-MISC -4
p=TO+t=I-MISC -4
t=O+w=review 1
Oi=review+t=O 1
t=I-MISC+w=his -2
Oi=his+t=I-MISC -2
p=PRP$+t=I-MISC -2
t=I-MISC+w=after -1
Oi=after+t=I-MISC -3
p=IN+t=I-MISC -1
t=I-MISC+w=EU -3
Oi=eu+t=I-MISC -3
t=I-MISC+w='s 2
Oi='s+t=I-MISC 1
p=POS+t=I-MISC 0
t=O+w=standing 1
Oi=standing+t=O 1
t=I-MISC+w=veterinary -1
Oi=veterinary+t=I-MISC -1
t=I-MISC+w=, 1
Oi=,+t=I-MISC 1
p=,+t=I-MISC 1
t=O+w=mational 0
Oi=mational+t=O 0
t=I-MISC+w=animal -1
Oi=animal+t=I-MISC -1
p=NN+t=I-MISC -1
t=I-MISC+w=officials -1
Oi=officials+t=I-MISC -1
p=NNS+t=I-MISC 1
t=I-MISC+w=questioned -1
Oi=questioned+t=I-MISC -1
p=VBD+t=I-MISC -4
t=I-MISC+w=such -1
Oi=such+t=I-MISC -1
t=I-MISC+w=justified -1
Oi=justified+t=I-MISC -1
p=VBN+t=I-MISC -5
t=O+w=as 3
Oi=as+t=O 9
t=I-MISC+w=there -1
Oi=there+t=I-MISC -1
p=RB+t=I-MISC -3
t=I-MISC+w=only -1
Oi=only+t=I-MISC -1
t=I-MISC+w=slight -1
Oi=slight+t=I-MISC -1
t=O+w=risk 1
Oi=risk+t=O 1
t=I-MISC+w=human -1
Oi=human+t=I-MISC -1
t=O+w=his 4
Oi=his+t=O 4
p=PRP$+t=O 9
t=O+w=officials 2
Oi=officials+t=O 4
t=O+w=questioned 1
Oi=questioned+t=O 1
t=O+w=justified 1
Oi=justified+t=O 1
t=O+w=there 1
Oi=there+t=O 2
t=O+w=only 3
Oi=only+t=O 4
t=O+w=slight 2
Oi=slight+t=O -2
t=O+w=Spanish -4
Oi=spanish+t=O -4
t=O+w=Minister 14
Oi=minister+t=O 14
t=O+w=Loyola -1
Oi=loyola+t=O -1
t=O+w=de 1
Oi=de+t=O -2
t=O+w=Palacio -1
Oi=palacio+t=O -1
t=O+w=had 3
Oi=had+t=O 3
t=O+w=earlier 4
Oi=earlier+t=O 4
p=RBR+t=O 4
t=O+w=accused 1
Oi=accused+t=O 1
t=O+w=at 0
Oi=at+t=O 13
t=O+w=an 7
Oi=an+t=O 7
t=O+w=farm 1
t=O+w=ministers 0
Oi=ministers+t=O 4
t=O+w=' 4
Oi='+t=O 4
t=O+w=meeting 2
Oi=meeting+t=O 7
t=O+w=of 2
Oi=of+t=O 2
t=O+w=causing 0
Oi=causing+t=O 0
p=VBG+t=O 3
t=O+w=unjustified 0
Oi=unjustified+t=O 0
t=O+w=alarm 1
Oi=alarm+t=O 0
t=O+w=through 2
Oi=through+t=O 2
t=O+w=dangerous 2
Oi=dangerous+t=O 2
t=O+w=generalisation 0
Oi=generalisation+t=O 0
t=I-MISC+w=Spanish 6
ti=I-MISC+ti-1=<START> -1
Oi=spanish+t=I-MISC 7
t=I-PER+w=Loyola 3
Oi=loyola+t=I-PER 3
t=I-PER+w=de 0
Oi=de+t=I-PER 0
t=I-PER+w=Palacio 3
Oi=palacio+t=I-PER 3
p=JJ+t=I-ORG -2
t=O+w=Only 1
t=O+w=backed 0
Oi=backed+t=O 0
t=I-PER+w=EU -1
Oi=eu+t=I-PER -1
t=O+w=multidisciplinary 0
Oi=multidisciplinary+t=O 0
t=O+w=committees 1
Oi=committees+t=O 1
t=O+w=are 2
Oi=are+t=O 2
t=O+w=due 3
Oi=due+t=O 3
t=O+w=re-examine 0
Oi=re-examine+t=O 0
t=O+w=issue 1
Oi=issue+t=O 3
t=O+w=early 3
Oi=early+t=O 4
t=O+w=next 1
Oi=next+t=O 5
t=O+w=make 2
Oi=make+t=O 2
t=O+w=recommendations 0
Oi=recommendations+t=O 0
t=O+w=senior 0
Oi=senior+t=O 6
t=I-LOC+w=Sheep -1
Oi=sheep+t=I-LOC -1
t=O+w=have 3
Oi=have+t=O 7
t=O+w=long 2
Oi=long+t=O 4
t=O+w=been 0
Oi=been+t=O 0
t=O+w=known 0
Oi=known+t=O 0
t=O+w=scrapie 0
Oi=scrapie+t=O 0
t=O+w=brain-wasting 0
Oi=brain-wasting+t=O 0
t=O+w=similar 2
Oi=similar+t=O 2
t=I-LOC+w=BSE -1
Oi=bse+t=I-LOC -1
t=O+w=which 8
Oi=which+t=O 8
t=O+w=is 2
Oi=is+t=O 2
t=O+w=believed 0
Oi=believed+t=O 0
t=O+w=transferred 0
Oi=transferred+t=O 0
t=O+w=cattle 0
Oi=cattle+t=O 0
t=O+w=feed 1
Oi=feed+t=O 1
t=O+w=containing 0
Oi=containing+t=O 0
t=O+w=waste 0
Oi=waste+t=O 0
t=O+w=Sheep 4
t=O+w=British -8
Oi=british+t=O -8
t=O+w=farmers 1
Oi=farmers+t=O 1
t=O+w=denied 0
Oi=denied+t=O 0
p=EX+t=O 1
t=O+w=danger 0
Oi=danger+t=O 0
t=O+w=their 1
Oi=their+t=O 4
t=O+w=but 0
t=O+w=expressed 0
Oi=expressed+t=O 0
t=O+w=concern 3
Oi=concern+t=O 3
t=O+w=German -9
Oi=german+t=O -10
t=O+w=government 5
Oi=government+t=O 5
t=O+w=avoid 0
Oi=avoid+t=O 0
t=O+w=might 1
Oi=might+t=O 1
t=O+w=influence 0
Oi=influence+t=O 0
t=O+w=across 4
Oi=across+t=O -3
t=O+w=Europe -4
Oi=europe+t=O -4
t=I-LOC+w=Europe 4
Oi=europe+t=I-LOC 4
t=O+w=What 0
Oi=what+t=O 2
p=WP+t=O 3
t=O+w=extremely 0
Oi=extremely+t=O 0
t=O+w=careful 0
Oi=careful+t=O 0
t=O+w=how 1
Oi=how+t=O 1
p=WRB+t=O 1
t=O+w=going 1
Oi=going+t=O 1
t=O+w=take 1
Oi=take+t=O 4
t=I-PER+w=Germany -3
Oi=germany+t=I-PER -3
t=O+w=lead 2
Oi=lead+t=O 6
t=I-PER+w=Welsh -2
Oi=welsh+t=I-PER -2
t=I-MISC+w=National 1
ti=I-MISC+ti-1=I-PER -7
Oi=national+t=I-MISC 2
t=I-PER+w=Farmers -1
ti=I-PER+ti-1=I-MISC 0
Oi=farmers+t=I-PER -1
t=I-LOC+w=Union 4
Oi=union+t=I-LOC 4
t=I-PER+w=NFU -1
Oi=nfu+t=I-PER -1
t=O+w=chairman 0
Oi=chairman+t=O 7
t=I-PER+w=John 9
Oi=john+t=I-PER 9
t=I-MISC+w=Lloyd -2
Oi=lloyd+t=I-MISC -2
t=I-PER+w=Jones 4
Oi=jones+t=I-PER 4
t=I-PER+w=BBC -1
Oi=bbc+t=I-PER -1
t=O+w=radio 0
Oi=radio+t=O -1
t=I-ORG+w=Welsh -1
Oi=welsh+t=I-ORG -1
t=I-ORG+w=National 6
Oi=national+t=I-ORG 0
t=I-ORG+w=Farmers 4
Oi=farmers+t=I-ORG 4
t=I-ORG+w=' -2
Oi='+t=I-ORG -2
p=POS+t=I-ORG 1
t=I-ORG+w=NFU 3
Oi=nfu+t=I-ORG 3
t=I-PER+w=Lloyd 1
Oi=lloyd+t=I-PER 1
t=I-ORG+w=BBC 5
Oi=bbc+t=I-ORG 5
t=I-ORG+w=radio 0
Oi=radio+t=I-ORG 7
p=NN+t=I-ORG -1
t=I-ORG+w=Bonn -2
Oi=bonn+t=I-ORG -2
t=O+w=has 4
Oi=has+t=O 1
t=O+w=led 1
Oi=led+t=O 1
t=O+w=efforts 1
Oi=efforts+t=O 1
t=O+w=public 3
Oi=public+t=O 4
t=O+w=consumer 2
Oi=consumer+t=O -1
t=O+w=confidence 1
Oi=confidence+t=O 1
t=O+w=collapsed 0
Oi=collapsed+t=O 0
t=O+w=in 5
Oi=in+t=O 8
t=I-ORG+w=March -2
Oi=march+t=I-ORG -2
t=O+w=report 3
Oi=report+t=O 3
t=O+w=suggested 0
Oi=suggested+t=O 0
t=O+w=humans 0
Oi=humans+t=O 0
t=O+w=illness 1
Oi=illness+t=O 6
t=O+w=eating 0
Oi=eating+t=O 0
t=O+w=contaminated 0
Oi=contaminated+t=O 0
t=O+w=beef 1
Oi=beef+t=O 1
t=I-LOC+w=Bonn 3
Oi=bonn+t=I-LOC 10
t=O+w=March 6
Oi=march+t=O 6
t=O+w=imported 0
Oi=imported+t=O 0
t=O+w=47,600 0
Oi=47,600+t=O 0
t=O+w=year 4
Oi=year+t=O 5
t=O+w=nearly 2
Oi=nearly+t=O 2
t=O+w=half 3
Oi=half+t=O 3
t=O+w=total 1
Oi=total+t=O 5
t=O+w=imports 0
Oi=imports+t=O 0
t=O+w=It 0
t=O+w=brought 1
Oi=brought+t=O 1
t=O+w=4,275 0
Oi=4,275+t=O 0
t=O+w=tonnes 1
Oi=tonnes+t=O 1
t=O+w=mutton 0
Oi=mutton+t=O 0
t=O+w=some 3
Oi=some+t=O 4
t=O+w=10 1
Oi=10+t=O 1
t=O+w=percent 5
Oi=percent+t=O 5
t=O+w=overall 1
Oi=overall+t=O 1
t=I-MISC+w=-DOCSTART- -1
Oi=-docstart-+t=I-MISC -1
p=-X-+t=I-MISC -1
ti=<STOP>+ti-1=I-MISC -25
t=O+w=-DOCSTART- 3
Oi=-docstart-+t=O 3
p=-X-+t=O 3
t=I-ORG+w=Rare -1
Oi=rare+t=I-ORG -1
t=I-ORG+w=Hendrix -1
Oi=hendrix+t=I-ORG -1
t=O+w=song 1
Oi=song+t=O 1
t=O+w=draft 1
Oi=draft+t=O 1
t=O+w=sells 0
Oi=sells+t=O 0
t=O+w=almost 0
Oi=almost+t=O 0
t=O+w=$ 10
Oi=$+t=O 10
p=$+t=O -7
t=O+w=17,000 0
Oi=17,000+t=O 0
t=O+w=Rare 5
Oi=rare+t=O 5
t=I-PER+w=Hendrix 5
Oi=hendrix+t=I-PER 5
t=I-LOC+w=LONDON 9
Oi=london+t=I-LOC 11
t=O+w=A -1
t=O+w=rare 0
t=O+w=handwritten 0
Oi=handwritten+t=O 0
t=I-LOC+w=U.S. 6
Oi=u.s.+t=I-LOC 6
t=O+w=guitar 0
Oi=guitar+t=O 0
t=O+w=legend 1
Oi=legend+t=O 1
t=I-LOC+w=Jimi -1
Oi=jimi+t=I-LOC -1
t=I-LOC+w=Hendrix -1
ti=I-LOC+ti-1=I-LOC 6
Oi=hendrix+t=I-LOC -1
t=O+w=sold 1
Oi=sold+t=O 1
t=I-LOC+w=Thursday -3
Oi=thursday+t=I-LOC -3
t=O+w=auction 0
Oi=auction+t=O 4
t=O+w=late 3
Oi=late+t=O 3
t=O+w=musician 0
Oi=musician+t=O 0
t=O+w=favourite 2
Oi=favourite+t=O 3
t=O+w=possessions 0
Oi=possessions+t=O 0
t=I-PER+w=Jimi 2
Oi=jimi+t=I-PER 2
t=I-ORG+w=Florida 5
Oi=florida+t=I-ORG 4
t=O+w=restaurant 1
Oi=restaurant+t=O 1
t=O+w=paid 0
Oi=paid+t=O 0
t=O+w=10,925 0
Oi=10,925+t=O 0
t=O+w=pounds 2
Oi=pounds+t=O 2
t=O+w=16,935 0
Oi=16,935+t=O 0
t=O+w=Ai -7
Oi=ai+t=O -7
t=O+w=no 4
Oi=no+t=O 3
t=O+w=telling -2
Oi=telling+t=O -2
t=O+w=penned 0
Oi=penned+t=O 0
t=O+w=piece 0
Oi=piece+t=O 0
t=I-ORG+w=London 4
Oi=london+t=I-ORG -1
t=O+w=hotel 0
Oi=hotel+t=O 2
t=O+w=stationery 0
Oi=stationery+t=O 0
t=O+w=1966 0
Oi=1966+t=O 0
t=I-LOC+w=Florida 1
Oi=florida+t=I-LOC 5
t=I-MISC+w=Ai 4
Oi=ai+t=I-MISC 4
p=VBZ+t=I-MISC 1
t=I-MISC+w=n't 3
Oi=n't+t=I-MISC 3
t=I-MISC+w=no 0
Oi=no+t=I-MISC 2
p=DT+t=I-MISC 1
t=I-MISC+w=telling 4
Oi=telling+t=I-MISC 4
p=VBG+t=I-MISC -3
t=I-LOC+w=London 2
t=O+w=At 0
t=O+w=end 0
Oi=end+t=O 5
t=I-LOC+w=January -3
Oi=january+t=I-LOC -3
t=O+w=1967 1
Oi=1967+t=O 1
t=O+w=concert 1
Oi=concert+t=O 1
t=O+w=English -4
Oi=english+t=O -9
t=O+w=city 7
Oi=city+t=O -4
t=I-LOC+w=Nottingham 3
Oi=nottingham+t=I-LOC 3
t=O+w=he 6
t=O+w=threw 0
Oi=threw+t=O 0
t=O+w=sheet 1
Oi=sheet+t=O 6
t=O+w=paper 1
Oi=paper+t=O 1
t=O+w=into 2
Oi=into+t=O 5
t=O+w=audience 1
Oi=audience+t=O 1
t=O+w=where 2
Oi=where+t=O 2
t=O+w=retrieved 1
Oi=retrieved+t=O 1
t=O+w=fan 1
Oi=fan+t=O 1
t=O+w=January 8
Oi=january+t=O 8
t=I-MISC+w=English 7
Oi=english+t=I-MISC 12
t=O+w=Buyers 0
Oi=buyers+t=O 0
t=O+w=also 5
Oi=also+t=O 5
t=O+w=snapped 0
Oi=snapped+t=O 0
t=O+w=up 4
Oi=up+t=O 5
t=O+w=16 -3
Oi=16+t=O -3
t=O+w=items 0
Oi=items+t=O 0
t=O+w=were 3
Oi=were+t=O 3
t=O+w=put 0
Oi=put+t=O 5
p=RP+t=O 1
t=O+w=former 3
Oi=former+t=O 8
t=O+w=girlfriend 2
Oi=girlfriend+t=O 2
t=I-LOC+w=Kathy -1
Oi=kathy+t=I-LOC -1
t=I-PER+w=Etchingham 1
ti=I-PER+ti-1=I-LOC -15
Oi=etchingham+t=I-PER 1
t=O+w=who 3
Oi=who+t=O 3
t=O+w=lived 0
Oi=lived+t=O 0
t=O+w=him 2
Oi=him+t=O 2
t=O+w=1969 0
Oi=1969+t=O 0
t=I-PER+w=Kathy 2
Oi=kathy+t=I-PER 2
t=O+w=They 0
Oi=they+t=O 3
t=O+w=included 0
Oi=included+t=O 0
t=O+w=black 3
Oi=black+t=O 2
t=O+w=lacquer 0
Oi=lacquer+t=O 0
t=O+w=mother 2
Oi=mother+t=O 1
t=O+w=pearl 0
Oi=pearl+t=O 0
t=O+w=inlaid 0
Oi=inlaid+t=O 0
t=O+w=box 0
Oi=box+t=O 0
t=O+w=used 1
Oi=used+t=O 4
t=O+w=store 1
Oi=store+t=O 1
t=O+w=drugs 0
Oi=drugs+t=O 0
t=O+w=anonymous 2
Oi=anonymous+t=O 2
t=O+w=Australian -10
Oi=australian+t=O -10
t=O+w=purchaser 0
Oi=purchaser+t=O 0
t=O+w=bought 0
Oi=bought+t=O 0
t=O+w=5,060 0
Oi=5,060+t=O 0
t=O+w=7,845 0
Oi=7,845+t=O 0
t=I-MISC+w=Australian 8
Oi=australian+t=I-MISC 13
t=I-LOC+w=The 3
Oi=the+t=I-LOC 1
p=DT+t=I-LOC 3
t=O+w=guitarist 0
Oi=guitarist+t=O 0
t=O+w=died 0
Oi=died+t=O 0
t=I-LOC+w=a -4
Oi=a+t=I-LOC -5
t=O+w=overdose 0
Oi=overdose+t=O 0
t=O+w=1970 0
Oi=1970+t=O 0
t=O+w=aged 0
Oi=aged+t=O 0
t=O+w=27 1
Oi=27+t=O 1
t=I-PER+w=China -2
Oi=china+t=I-PER -2
t=O+w=says 2
Oi=says+t=O 2
t=I-PER+w=Taiwan -3
Oi=taiwan+t=I-PER -3
t=O+w=spoils 0
Oi=spoils+t=O 0
t=O+w=atmosphere 1
Oi=atmosphere+t=O 1
t=O+w=talks 2
Oi=talks+t=O 2
t=I-LOC+w=China 6
Oi=china+t=I-LOC 5
t=I-LOC+w=Taiwan 6
Oi=taiwan+t=I-LOC 6
t=O+w=BEIJING -4
Oi=beijing+t=O -4
t=I-LOC+w=BEIJING 4
Oi=beijing+t=I-LOC 6
p=VBG+t=I-LOC 1
t=I-LOC+w=Taipei 3
Oi=taipei+t=I-LOC 4
t=I-LOC+w=spoiling -1
Oi=spoiling+t=I-LOC -1
t=O+w=resumption 0
Oi=resumption+t=O 0
t=I-LOC+w=Strait 3
Oi=strait+t=I-LOC 3
t=O+w=visit 3
Oi=visit+t=O 3
t=I-LOC+w=Ukraine 8
Oi=ukraine+t=I-LOC 8
t=I-ORG+w=Taiwanese -1
Oi=taiwanese+t=I-ORG -1
t=I-ORG+w=Vice -1
Oi=vice+t=I-ORG -1
t=I-ORG+w=President -4
Oi=president+t=I-ORG -4
t=I-ORG+w=Lien -1
Oi=lien+t=I-ORG -1
t=I-LOC+w=Chan -1
ti=I-LOC+ti-1=I-ORG -7
Oi=chan+t=I-LOC -1
t=O+w=this 3
Oi=this+t=O 7
t=O+w=week 4
Oi=week+t=O 6
t=O+w=infuriated 0
Oi=infuriated+t=O 0
t=I-LOC+w=Beijing 2
t=O+w=spoiling 1
Oi=spoiling+t=O 1
t=I-MISC+w=Taiwanese 7
Oi=taiwanese+t=I-MISC 7
t=O+w=Vice 6
Oi=vice+t=O 6
t=O+w=President 9
Oi=president+t=O 9
t=I-PER+w=Lien 3
Oi=lien+t=I-PER 3
t=I-PER+w=Chan 2
Oi=chan+t=I-PER 2
t=O+w=Speaking 1
Oi=speaking+t=O 1
t=O+w=hours 3
Oi=hours+t=O 3
t=O+w=Chinese -4
Oi=chinese+t=O -4
t=O+w=state 3
Oi=state+t=O 5
t=O+w=media 0
Oi=media+t=O 2
t=O+w=time 3
Oi=time+t=O 2
t=O+w=right 2
Oi=right+t=O 2
t=O+w=engage 0
Oi=engage+t=O 0
t=O+w=political 3
Oi=political+t=O 3
t=I-PER+w=Foreign -5
Oi=foreign+t=I-PER -5
t=I-LOC+w=Ministry -2
ti=I-LOC+ti-1=I-PER -4
Oi=ministry+t=I-LOC -2
t=I-PER+w=Shen 0
Oi=shen+t=I-PER 0
t=I-LOC+w=Guofang -1
Oi=guofang+t=I-LOC -1
t=I-PER+w=Reuters -3
Oi=reuters+t=I-PER -3
t=O+w=: 1
Oi=:+t=O 1
t=O+w=necessary 0
Oi=necessary+t=O 0
t=O+w=opening 2
Oi=opening+t=O 2
t=O+w=disrupted 0
Oi=disrupted+t=O 0
t=O+w=authorities 1
Oi=authorities+t=O 5
t=I-MISC+w=Chinese 6
Oi=chinese+t=I-MISC 6
t=I-ORG+w=Foreign 4
Oi=foreign+t=I-ORG 3
t=I-ORG+w=Ministry 6
Oi=ministry+t=I-ORG 7
t=I-PER+w=Guofang 5
Oi=guofang+t=I-PER 5
t=I-ORG+w=Reuters 10
Oi=reuters+t=I-ORG 10
t=O+w=State 2
t=O+w=quoted 2
Oi=quoted+t=O 2
t=I-ORG+w=China -1
Oi=china+t=I-ORG 0
t=O+w=top 2
Oi=top+t=O 6
t=O+w=negotiator 1
Oi=negotiator+t=O 1
t=I-ORG+w=Taipei -1
Oi=taipei+t=I-ORG -1
t=I-ORG+w=Tang -2
Oi=tang+t=I-ORG -2
t=I-ORG+w=Shubei -1
Oi=shubei+t=I-ORG -1
t=O+w=visiting 2
Oi=visiting+t=O 2
t=O+w=group 6
Oi=group+t=O 6
t=O+w=rivals 1
Oi=rivals+t=O 1
t=O+w=hold 2
Oi=hold+t=O 4
t=I-PER+w=Tang 3
Oi=tang+t=I-PER 3
t=I-PER+w=Shubei 2
Oi=shubei+t=I-PER 2
t=O+w=Now 0
Oi=now+t=O 2
t=O+w=two 4
Oi=two+t=O -2
t=O+w=sides 2
Oi=sides+t=O 2
t=O+w=... 0
Oi=...+t=O 0
t=O+w=hostility 0
Oi=hostility+t=O 0
t=O+w=overseas 1
Oi=overseas+t=O 2
t=O+w=edition 0
Oi=edition+t=O 0
t=O+w=People -5
Oi=people+t=O -2
p=NNPS+t=O -8
t=O+w=Daily -2
Oi=daily+t=O 2
t=I-LOC+w=Tang -1
Oi=tang+t=I-LOC -1
t=O+w=saying 1
Oi=saying+t=O 1
t=I-ORG+w=People 5
Oi=people+t=I-ORG 3
p=NNPS+t=I-ORG 4
t=I-ORG+w='s -5
Oi='s+t=I-ORG 0
t=I-ORG+w=Daily 10
Oi=daily+t=I-ORG 8
t=O+w=foreign 1
Oi=foreign+t=O 8
t=O+w=ministry 0
Oi=ministry+t=O 4
t=I-LOC+w=Shen -2
Oi=shen+t=I-LOC -2
t=I-LOC+w=Reuters -4
Oi=reuters+t=I-LOC -4
t=I-PER+w=Television -1
Oi=television+t=I-PER -3
t=O+w=interview 1
Oi=interview+t=O 1
t=O+w=read 0
Oi=read+t=O 0
t=O+w=comments 0
Oi=comments+t=O 0
t=O+w=gave 1
Oi=gave+t=O 1
t=O+w=details 2
Oi=details+t=O 2
t=O+w=why 1
Oi=why+t=O 1
t=O+w=considered 0
Oi=considered+t=O 0
t=O+w=considers 0
Oi=considers+t=O 0
t=O+w=renegade 0
Oi=renegade+t=O 0
t=O+w=province 2
Oi=province+t=O 1
t=I-ORG+w=Shen 4
Oi=shen+t=I-ORG 4
t=I-ORG+w=Television 5
Oi=television+t=I-ORG 3
t=O+w=opposed 0
Oi=opposed+t=O 0
t=O+w=all 7
Oi=all+t=O 5
t=O+w=gain 0
Oi=gain+t=O 0
t=O+w=greater 1
Oi=greater+t=O 4
t=O+w=international 5
Oi=international+t=O 6
t=O+w=recognition 1
Oi=recognition+t=O 1
t=I-ORG+w=Ukraine -2
Oi=ukraine+t=I-ORG -2
t=I-MISC+w=Vice -2
Oi=vice+t=I-MISC -2
t=I-MISC+w=President 2
Oi=president+t=I-MISC 2
t=I-MISC+w=Lien -1
Oi=lien+t=I-MISC -1
t=O+w=rival 1
Oi=rival+t=O 1
t=O+w=island 3
Oi=island+t=O 2
t=O+w=practical 1
Oi=practical+t=O 1
t=O+w=steps 0
Oi=steps+t=O 4
t=O+w=towards 0
Oi=towards+t=O 3
t=O+w=goal 1
Oi=goal+t=O 1
t=O+w=Consultations 0
Oi=consultations+t=O 0
t=O+w=held 2
Oi=held+t=O -3
t=O+w=set 1
Oi=set+t=O 1
t=O+w=format 0
Oi=format+t=O 0
t=O+w=official 4
Oi=official+t=O 4
t=I-PER+w=Xinhua -2
Oi=xinhua+t=I-PER -2
t=O+w=agency 6
Oi=agency+t=O 1
t=I-LOC+w=Shubei -1
Oi=shubei+t=I-LOC -1
t=O+w=executive 1
Oi=executive+t=O 5
t=O+w=vice 0
t=I-PER+w=Association -4
Oi=association+t=I-PER -4
t=I-PER+w=Relations -2
Oi=relations+t=I-PER -2
t=O+w=Across -7
t=I-PER+w=Straits -1
Oi=straits+t=I-PER -1
t=I-PER+w=Wednesday -6
Oi=wednesday+t=I-PER -6
t=I-ORG+w=Xinhua 5
Oi=xinhua+t=I-ORG 5
t=I-ORG+w=Association 10
Oi=association+t=I-ORG 6
t=I-ORG+w=for 2
Oi=for+t=I-ORG 0
p=IN+t=I-ORG -2
t=I-ORG+w=Relations -2
Oi=relations+t=I-ORG -3
t=I-ORG+w=Across 7
Oi=across+t=I-ORG 3
t=I-ORG+w=the -5
Oi=the+t=I-ORG -2
p=DT+t=I-ORG 2
t=I-ORG+w=Taiwan 2
Oi=taiwan+t=I-ORG 2
t=I-ORG+w=Straits 0
Oi=straits+t=I-ORG 0
t=I-ORG+w=German 2
Oi=german+t=I-ORG 0
t=I-ORG+w=July -4
Oi=july+t=I-ORG -4
t=I-ORG+w=car -1
Oi=car+t=I-ORG -1
t=I-ORG+w=registrations -2
Oi=registrations+t=I-ORG -2
p=NNS+t=I-ORG -4
t=I-ORG+w=up -2
Oi=up+t=I-ORG -2
p=RB+t=I-ORG -2
t=I-ORG+w=14.2 -1
Oi=14.2+t=I-ORG -1
p=CD+t=I-ORG -4
t=I-ORG+w=pct -1
Oi=pct+t=I-ORG -4
t=O+w=yr 2
Oi=yr+t=O 7
t=O+w=/ 0
Oi=/+t=O 0
p=SYM+t=O 9
t=O+w=July 10
Oi=july+t=O 11
t=O+w=car 2
Oi=car+t=O 2
t=O+w=registrations 2
Oi=registrations+t=O 2
t=O+w=14.2 1
Oi=14.2+t=O 1
t=O+w=pct 1
Oi=pct+t=O 9
t=I-MISC+w=FRANKFURT -1
Oi=frankfurt+t=I-MISC -2
t=I-LOC+w=FRANKFURT 4
Oi=frankfurt+t=I-LOC 7
t=O+w=first-time 3
Oi=first-time+t=O 3
t=O+w=motor -3
Oi=motor+t=O 2
t=O+w=vehicles -2
Oi=vehicles+t=O -2
t=O+w=jumped 0
Oi=jumped+t=O 0
t=O+w=year-earlier 1
Oi=year-earlier+t=O 1
t=O+w=period 3
Oi=period+t=O 3
t=O+w=Federal 1
Oi=federal+t=O 4
t=O+w=office 1
Oi=office+t=O 1
t=I-ORG+w=Federal 4
Oi=federal+t=I-ORG 2
t=I-ORG+w=office -1
Oi=office+t=I-ORG 2
t=I-ORG+w=motor 6
Oi=motor+t=I-ORG 3
t=I-ORG+w=vehicles 3
Oi=vehicles+t=I-ORG 3
t=O+w=356,725 1
Oi=356,725+t=O 1
t=O+w=new 6
Oi=new+t=O 2
t=O+w=cars 4
Oi=cars+t=O 4
t=O+w=registered 1
Oi=registered+t=O 1
t=I-ORG+w=in 3
Oi=in+t=I-ORG 2
t=O+w=1996 -1
Oi=1996+t=O -1
t=O+w=304,850 1
Oi=304,850+t=O 1
t=O+w=passenger 2
Oi=passenger+t=O 2
t=O+w=15,613 1
Oi=15,613+t=O 1
t=O+w=trucks 2
Oi=trucks+t=O 2
t=O+w=figures 1
Oi=figures+t=O 4
t=O+w=represent 1
Oi=represent+t=O 1
t=O+w=13.6 1
Oi=13.6+t=O 1
t=O+w=increase 1
Oi=increase+t=O 1
t=O+w=2.2 1
Oi=2.2+t=O 1
t=O+w=decline 1
Oi=decline+t=O 1
t=O+w=1995 2
Oi=1995+t=O 2
t=O+w=Motor-bike 0
Oi=motor-bike+t=O 0
t=O+w=registration 1
Oi=registration+t=O 1
t=O+w=rose 0
Oi=rose+t=O 0
t=O+w=32.7 0
Oi=32.7+t=O 0
t=O+w=growth 0
Oi=growth+t=O 0
t=O+w=partly 1
Oi=partly+t=O 1
t=O+w=increased 0
Oi=increased+t=O 0
t=O+w=number 3
Oi=number+t=O 3
t=O+w=Germans -4
Oi=germans+t=O -4
t=O+w=buying 6
Oi=buying+t=O 6
t=O+w=abroad 1
Oi=abroad+t=O 1
t=O+w=while 2
Oi=while+t=O 3
t=O+w=manufacturers 1
Oi=manufacturers+t=O 1
t=O+w=domestic 1
Oi=domestic+t=O 2
t=O+w=demand 2
Oi=demand+t=O 2
t=O+w=weak 1
Oi=weak+t=O 1
t=O+w=federal 3
t=I-MISC+w=Germans 5
Oi=germans+t=I-MISC 5
p=NNPS+t=I-MISC 5
t=O+w=Almost 0
t=O+w=posted 0
Oi=posted+t=O 0
t=O+w=gains 1
Oi=gains+t=O 2
t=O+w=numbers 1
Oi=numbers+t=O 1
t=I-ORG+w=Volkswagen 5
Oi=volkswagen+t=I-ORG 5
t=I-ORG+w=AG 7
Oi=ag+t=I-ORG 7
t=O+w=won 1
Oi=won+t=O 1
t=O+w=77,719 0
Oi=77,719+t=O 0
t=O+w=slightly 1
Oi=slightly+t=O 1
t=O+w=more 2
Oi=more+t=O 3
t=O+w=quarter 3
Oi=quarter+t=O 6
t=I-ORG+w=Opel 1
Oi=opel+t=I-ORG 1
t=I-ORG+w=together -2
Oi=together+t=I-ORG -2
t=I-ORG+w=with -5
Oi=with+t=I-ORG -5
t=I-ORG+w=General 1
Oi=general+t=I-ORG 1
t=I-ORG+w=Motors 5
Oi=motors+t=I-ORG 5
t=O+w=came 0
Oi=came+t=O 0
t=O+w=second 4
Oi=second+t=O 11
t=O+w=place 2
Oi=place+t=O 2
t=O+w=49,269 0
Oi=49,269+t=O 0
t=O+w=16.4 0
Oi=16.4+t=O 0
t=O+w=figure 0
Oi=figure+t=O 0
t=O+w=together 2
Oi=together+t=O 2
t=I-MISC+w=Third 3
Oi=third+t=I-MISC -1
t=I-ORG+w=Ford 6
Oi=ford+t=I-ORG 6
t=O+w=35,563 0
Oi=35,563+t=O 0
t=O+w=or 3
Oi=or+t=O 0
t=O+w=11.7 0
Oi=11.7+t=O 0
t=O+w=Third -3
Oi=third+t=O 10
t=I-ORG+w=Seat 9
Oi=seat+t=I-ORG 4
t=I-ORG+w=Porsche 3
Oi=porsche+t=I-ORG 3
t=O+w=fewer 2
Oi=fewer+t=O 2
t=O+w=compared 0
Oi=compared+t=O 0
t=O+w=Seat -9
Oi=seat+t=O -4
t=O+w=3,420 0
Oi=3,420+t=O 0
t=O+w=5522 0
Oi=5522+t=O 0
t=I-LOC+w=Porsche -1
Oi=porsche+t=I-LOC -1
t=O+w=fell 0
Oi=fell+t=O 0
t=O+w=554 0
Oi=554+t=O 0
t=O+w=643 0
Oi=643+t=O 0
t=O+w=GREEK -2
Oi=greek+t=O -6
t=O+w=SOCIALISTS 0
Oi=socialists+t=O 4
t=O+w=GIVE 0
Oi=give+t=O 1
t=I-ORG+w=GREEN -2
Oi=green+t=I-ORG -2
t=I-ORG+w=LIGHT -2
Oi=light+t=I-ORG -2
t=O+w=TO 3
t=I-ORG+w=PM -3
Oi=pm+t=I-ORG -3
t=O+w=FOR 3
t=O+w=ELECTIONS 0
Oi=elections+t=O 0
t=I-MISC+w=GREEK 2
Oi=greek+t=I-MISC 8
t=O+w=GREEN 5
Oi=green+t=O 3
t=O+w=LIGHT 5
Oi=light+t=O 5
t=O+w=PM 7
Oi=pm+t=O 7
t=O+w=ATHENS -6
Oi=athens+t=O -7
t=I-LOC+w=ATHENS 8
Oi=athens+t=I-LOC 8
p=NNS+t=I-LOC -1
t=O+w=Greek -4
t=O+w=socialist 0
Oi=socialist+t=O 6
t=O+w=party 2
Oi=party+t=O 3
t=O+w=bureau 0
Oi=bureau+t=O 0
t=O+w=green 0
t=O+w=light 0
t=O+w=Prime 10
Oi=prime+t=O 10
t=O+w=Costas -5
Oi=costas+t=O -5
t=O+w=Simitis -3
Oi=simitis+t=O -3
t=O+w=snap 0
Oi=snap+t=O 0
t=O+w=elections 4
t=O+w=its 2
Oi=its+t=O 2
t=O+w=general 3
Oi=general+t=O 8
t=O+w=secretary 1
Oi=secretary+t=O 11
t=O+w=Skandalidis -3
Oi=skandalidis+t=O -3
t=O+w=reporters 1
Oi=reporters+t=O 1
t=I-MISC+w=Greek 6
t=I-PER+w=Costas 6
Oi=costas+t=I-PER 6
p=VBZ+t=I-PER -2
t=I-PER+w=Simitis 4
Oi=simitis+t=I-PER 4
p=NNPS+t=I-PER 3
t=I-PER+w=Skandalidis 5
Oi=skandalidis+t=I-PER 5
t=I-MISC+w=Prime -2
Oi=prime+t=I-MISC -2
t=I-MISC+w=Minister -1
Oi=minister+t=I-MISC -1
t=I-MISC+w=Costas -1
Oi=costas+t=I-MISC -1
t=I-MISC+w=Simitis -1
Oi=simitis+t=I-MISC -1
t=I-ORG+w=going -1
Oi=going+t=I-ORG -1
p=VBG+t=I-ORG -1
t=I-MISC+w=official -1
Oi=official+t=I-MISC -1
t=O+w=announcement 3
Oi=announcement+t=O 3
t=I-ORG+w=cabinet -1
Oi=cabinet+t=I-ORG 4
t=I-ORG+w=meeting -1
Oi=meeting+t=I-ORG -1
t=O+w=later 2
Oi=later+t=O 2
t=I-ORG+w=Thursday -2
Oi=thursday+t=I-ORG -4
t=I-ORG+w=Skandalidis -2
Oi=skandalidis+t=I-ORG -2
t=O+w=cabinet 1
Oi=cabinet+t=O 3
t=O+w=Dimitris -2
Oi=dimitris+t=O -2
t=O+w=Kontogiannis -2
Oi=kontogiannis+t=O -2
t=O+w=Athens -1
t=O+w=Newsroom -4
Oi=newsroom+t=O 2
t=O+w=+301 6
Oi=+301+t=O 6
t=O+w=3311812-4 0
Oi=3311812-4+t=O 0
t=I-PER+w=Dimitris 3
Oi=dimitris+t=I-PER 3
t=I-PER+w=Kontogiannis 3
Oi=kontogiannis+t=I-PER 3
t=I-ORG+w=Athens 1
Oi=athens+t=I-ORG 0
t=I-ORG+w=Newsroom 14
Oi=newsroom+t=I-ORG 8
t=I-LOC+w=-DOCSTART- -1
Oi=-docstart-+t=I-LOC -1
p=-X-+t=I-LOC -1
ti=<STOP>+ti-1=I-LOC 21
t=O+w=BayerVB -5
Oi=bayervb+t=O -5
t=O+w=sets 1
Oi=sets+t=O 1
t=O+w=C$ -2
Oi=c$+t=O -2
t=O+w=100 -2
Oi=100+t=O -2
t=O+w=million 2
Oi=million+t=O 3
t=O+w=six-year 1
Oi=six-year+t=O 1
t=O+w=bond 1
Oi=bond+t=O 0
t=I-ORG+w=BayerVB 5
Oi=bayervb+t=I-ORG 5
t=I-MISC+w=C$ 2
Oi=c$+t=I-MISC 2
p=$+t=I-MISC 12
t=I-PER+w=LONDON -1
Oi=london+t=I-PER -3
t=O+w=following 2
Oi=following+t=O 2
t=O+w=announced 0
Oi=announced+t=O 0
t=O+w=manager 3
Oi=manager+t=O 3
t=I-PER+w=Toronto -1
Oi=toronto+t=I-PER -2
t=I-PER+w=Dominion 5
Oi=dominion+t=I-PER 5
t=I-PER+w=BORROWER -2
Oi=borrower+t=I-PER -2
t=B-LOC+w=BAYERISCHE -1
ti=B-LOC+ti-1=I-PER -1
Oi=bayerische+t=B-LOC -1
p=NNP+t=B-LOC -3
t=I-PER+w=VEREINSBANK -2
ti=I-PER+ti-1=B-LOC -2
Oi=vereinsbank+t=I-PER -2
t=O+w=BORROWER 6
Oi=borrower+t=O 6
t=I-ORG+w=BAYERISCHE 7
Oi=bayerische+t=I-ORG 7
t=I-ORG+w=VEREINSBANK 7
Oi=vereinsbank+t=I-ORG 7
t=I-LOC+w=AMT -2
Oi=amt+t=I-LOC -2
t=I-PER+w=MLN -2
Oi=mln+t=I-PER -2
t=O+w=COUPON 0
Oi=coupon+t=O 1
t=O+w=6.625 0
Oi=6.625+t=O 0
t=I-PER+w=MATURITY -1
Oi=maturity+t=I-PER -1
t=O+w=24.SEP.02 0
Oi=24.sep.02+t=O 0
t=O+w=AMT 5
Oi=amt+t=O 5
t=O+w=MLN 3
Oi=mln+t=O 4
t=O+w=MATURITY 4
Oi=maturity+t=O 4
t=I-ORG+w=TYPE -3
Oi=type+t=I-ORG -3
t=I-ORG+w=STRAIGHT -3
Oi=straight+t=I-ORG -3
t=I-ORG+w=ISS 3
Oi=iss+t=I-ORG 3
t=I-ORG+w=PRICE -5
Oi=price+t=I-ORG -7
t=O+w=100.92 0
Oi=100.92+t=O 0
t=O+w=PAY 1
Oi=pay+t=O 3
t=O+w=DATE 5
Oi=date+t=O 6
t=O+w=24.SEP.96 0
Oi=24.sep.96+t=O 0
t=O+w=TYPE 6
Oi=type+t=O 6
t=O+w=STRAIGHT 6
Oi=straight+t=O 6
t=O+w=ISS 3
Oi=iss+t=O 3
t=O+w=PRICE 7
Oi=price+t=O 8
t=O+w=FULL 2
Oi=full+t=O 3
t=O+w=FEES 0
Oi=fees+t=O 0
t=O+w=1.875 0
Oi=1.875+t=O 0
t=O+w=REOFFER 1
Oi=reoffer+t=O 1
t=O+w=99.32 0
Oi=99.32+t=O 0
t=O+w=SPREAD 1
Oi=spread+t=O 1
t=O+w=+20 0
Oi=+20+t=O 0
t=O+w=BP 2
Oi=bp+t=O 2
t=O+w=MOODY 0
Oi=moody+t=O -4
t=O+w=AA1 5
Oi=aa1+t=O 5
t=O+w=LISTING 5
Oi=listing+t=O 5
t=O+w=LUX 5
Oi=lux+t=O 5
t=O+w=FREQ 0
Oi=freq+t=O 0
t=O+w== 3
Oi==+t=O 3
t=O+w=S&P -8
Oi=s&p+t=O -8
t=O+w=DENOMS 1
Oi=denoms+t=O 1
t=O+w=K 0
Oi=k+t=O 0
t=O+w=1-10-100 0
Oi=1-10-100+t=O 0
t=O+w=SALE 3
Oi=sale+t=O 5
t=O+w=LIMITS 0
Oi=limits+t=O 1
t=O+w=US -8
Oi=us+t=O -5
t=O+w=UK -6
Oi=uk+t=O -6
t=O+w=CA -5
Oi=ca+t=O -5
t=I-ORG+w=S&P 7
Oi=s&p+t=I-ORG 7
t=I-LOC+w=US 5
Oi=us+t=I-LOC 4
t=I-LOC+w=UK 8
Oi=uk+t=I-LOC 8
t=I-LOC+w=CA 5
Oi=ca+t=I-LOC 5
p=VBN+t=I-LOC 2
t=I-LOC+w=NEG -2
Oi=neg+t=I-LOC -2
t=I-LOC+w=PLG -2
Oi=plg+t=I-LOC -2
t=O+w=NO 2
t=I-LOC+w=CRS -2
Oi=crs+t=I-LOC -2
t=I-LOC+w=DEFLT -2
Oi=deflt+t=I-LOC -2
t=O+w=FORCE 1
Oi=force+t=O 2
t=O+w=MAJ 0
Oi=maj+t=O 0
t=O+w=NEG 3
Oi=neg+t=O 3
t=O+w=PLG 3
Oi=plg+t=O 3
t=O+w=CRS 3
Oi=crs+t=O 3
t=O+w=DEFLT 3
Oi=deflt+t=O 3
t=O+w=GOV 0
Oi=gov+t=O 7
t=O+w=LAW 3
Oi=law+t=O 1
t=O+w=GERMAN -1
t=O+w=HOME 5
Oi=home+t=O 7
t=O+w=CTRY 0
Oi=ctry+t=O 0
t=O+w=TAX 0
Oi=tax+t=O 3
t=O+w=PROVS 0
Oi=provs+t=O 0
t=O+w=STANDARD 0
Oi=standard+t=O 1
t=I-MISC+w=GERMAN 5
t=O+w=MGT 1
Oi=mgt+t=O 1
t=O+w=UND 1
Oi=und+t=O 1
t=O+w=0.275 0
Oi=0.275+t=O 0
t=O+w=SELL 0
Oi=sell+t=O 1
t=O+w=CONC 1
Oi=conc+t=O 2
t=O+w=1.60 0
Oi=1.60+t=O 0
t=O+w=PRAECIP 1
Oi=praecip+t=O 1
t=O+w=UNDERLYING 0
Oi=underlying+t=O 0
t=O+w=GOVT 3
Oi=govt+t=O 3
t=O+w=BOND 1
t=O+w=7.0 0
Oi=7.0+t=O 0
t=O+w=PCT 8
t=O+w=SEPT 0
Oi=sept+t=O 8
t=O+w=2001 0
Oi=2001+t=O 0
t=O+w=NOTES 0
Oi=notes+t=O 2
t=O+w=BAYERISCHE -5
Oi=bayerische+t=O -5
t=O+w=VEREINSBANK -5
Oi=vereinsbank+t=O -5
t=O+w=IS 0
t=O+w=JOINT 0
Oi=joint+t=O 2
t=O+w=LEAD 3
t=O+w=MANAGER 0
p=VBP+t=I-ORG 0
t=O+w=London -4
Oi=london+t=O -7
t=I-MISC+w=Newsroom -1
Oi=newsroom+t=I-MISC -1
t=O+w=+44 0
Oi=+44+t=O 0
t=O+w=171 1
Oi=171+t=O 1
t=O+w=542 0
Oi=542+t=O 0
t=O+w=7658 0
Oi=7658+t=O 0
t=I-MISC+w=Venantius -1
Oi=venantius+t=I-MISC -1
t=I-ORG+w=$ -2
Oi=$+t=I-ORG -2
p=$+t=I-ORG -4
t=O+w=300 0
Oi=300+t=O 0
t=I-ORG+w=January -3
Oi=january+t=I-ORG -3
t=O+w=1999 0
Oi=1999+t=O 0
t=I-ORG+w=FRN -1
Oi=frn+t=I-ORG -1
t=I-ORG+w=Venantius 7
Oi=venantius+t=I-ORG 8
t=O+w=FRN 3
Oi=frn+t=O 3
t=O+w=LONDON -3
t=O+w=floating-rate 0
Oi=floating-rate+t=O 0
t=O+w=Lehman -3
Oi=lehman+t=O -3
t=O+w=Brothers -3
Oi=brothers+t=O -3
t=O+w=International -1
t=I-ORG+w=Lehman 4
Oi=lehman+t=I-ORG 4
t=I-ORG+w=Brothers 3
Oi=brothers+t=I-ORG 3
t=I-ORG+w=International 3
Oi=international+t=I-ORG -1
t=I-ORG+w=BORROWER -4
Oi=borrower+t=I-ORG -4
t=I-ORG+w=VENANTIUS 1
t=I-ORG+w=AB 2
Oi=ab+t=I-ORG 2
t=I-ORG+w=( -3
Oi=(+t=I-ORG -3
p=(+t=I-ORG -4
t=I-ORG+w=SWEDISH -2
Oi=swedish+t=I-ORG -3
t=I-ORG+w=NATIONAL -5
t=I-ORG+w=MORTGAGE -2
Oi=mortgage+t=I-ORG -2
t=O+w=AGENCY 0
t=I-MISC+w=SWEDISH 4
Oi=swedish+t=I-MISC 9
t=O+w=NATIONAL 1
Oi=national+t=O 5
t=O+w=MORTGAGE 3
Oi=mortgage+t=O 3
t=O+w=- 5
Oi=-+t=O 5
t=O+w=12.5 0
Oi=12.5+t=O 0
t=O+w=21.JAN.99 0
Oi=21.jan.99+t=O 0
t=O+w=BASE 3
Oi=base+t=O 3
t=O+w=3M -4
Oi=3m+t=O -4
t=O+w=LIBOR 2
Oi=libor+t=O 2
t=O+w=S23.SEP.96 2
Oi=s23.sep.96+t=O 2
t=I-ORG+w=3M 7
Oi=3m+t=I-ORG 7
t=O+w=LAST 4
t=I-LOC+w=AA3 -1
Oi=aa3+t=I-LOC -1
t=O+w=99.956 0
Oi=99.956+t=O 0
t=I-LOC+w=FULL -1
Oi=full+t=I-LOC -1
t=I-PER+w=BP -1
Oi=bp+t=I-PER -1
t=O+w=AA3 3
Oi=aa3+t=O 3
t=O+w=AA+ 2
Oi=aa++t=O 2
t=O+w=S 0
Oi=s+t=O 0
t=O+w=SHORT 4
Oi=short+t=O 5
t=O+w=FIRST 11
Oi=first+t=O 12
t=O+w=JP -6
Oi=jp+t=O -6
t=O+w=FR -5
Oi=fr+t=O -5
t=I-LOC+w=JP 7
Oi=jp+t=I-LOC 7
t=I-LOC+w=FR 5
Oi=fr+t=I-LOC 5
t=I-LOC+w=YES -1
Oi=yes+t=I-LOC -1
t=I-LOC+w=FORCE -1
Oi=force+t=I-LOC -2
p=VBP+t=I-LOC 2
t=I-LOC+w=IPMA -2
Oi=ipma+t=I-LOC -2
t=O+w=2 3
Oi=2+t=O 3
t=O+w=YES 1
Oi=yes+t=O 2
t=O+w=IPMA 2
Oi=ipma+t=O 2
t=O+w=ENGLISH -5
t=O+w=SWEDEN -4
Oi=sweden+t=O -6
t=I-MISC+w=ENGLISH 5
t=I-LOC+w=SWEDEN 4
Oi=sweden+t=I-LOC 10
t=I-ORG+w=MGT -1
Oi=mgt+t=I-ORG -1
t=I-MISC+w=UND -1
Oi=und+t=I-MISC -1
t=O+w=5 3
Oi=5+t=O 3
t=I-MISC+w=BP -1
Oi=bp+t=I-MISC -1
t=I-MISC+w=CONC -1
Oi=conc+t=I-MISC -1
t=I-MISC+w=PRAECIP -1
Oi=praecip+t=I-MISC -1
t=O+w=ISSUED 0
Oi=issued+t=O 1
t=O+w=OFF 4
Oi=off+t=O 6
t=O+w=EMTN 1
Oi=emtn+t=O 1
t=O+w=PROGRAMME 2
Oi=programme+t=O 2
t=O+w=8863 0
Oi=8863+t=O 0
t=O+w=Port 2
Oi=port+t=O 2
t=O+w=update 0
Oi=update+t=O 0
t=O+w=Syria -3
Oi=syria+t=O -3
t=O+w=Lloyds -4
Oi=lloyds+t=O -4
t=O+w=Shipping -4
Oi=shipping+t=O -3
t=I-LOC+w=Syria 4
Oi=syria+t=I-LOC 4
t=I-ORG+w=Lloyds 5
Oi=lloyds+t=I-ORG 5
t=I-ORG+w=Shipping 5
Oi=shipping+t=I-ORG 5
t=I-ORG+w=conditions -1
Oi=conditions+t=I-ORG -1
t=O+w=Intelligence 2
Oi=intelligence+t=O 2
t=I-ORG+w=Service 5
Oi=service+t=I-ORG 2
t=I-ORG+w=Intelligence 2
Oi=intelligence+t=I-ORG 2
t=O+w=LATTAKIA -2
Oi=lattakia+t=O -5
t=I-ORG+w=Aug -2
Oi=aug+t=I-ORG -3
t=O+w=waiting 1
Oi=waiting+t=O 1
t=I-ORG+w=Lattakia -1
Oi=lattakia+t=I-ORG -1
t=I-ORG+w=Tartous -1
Oi=tartous+t=I-ORG -1
t=O+w=presently 0
Oi=presently+t=O 0
t=O+w=24 0
Oi=24+t=O 0
t=I-LOC+w=LATTAKIA 2
Oi=lattakia+t=I-LOC 6
t=O+w=Aug 7
Oi=aug+t=O 12
t=I-LOC+w=Lattakia 4
t=I-LOC+w=Tartous 4
Oi=tartous+t=I-LOC 4
t=I-LOC+w=Israel 4
Oi=israel+t=I-LOC 4
t=O+w=plays 0
Oi=plays+t=O 0
t=O+w=down 2
Oi=down+t=O 2
t=O+w=fears 0
Oi=fears+t=O 0
t=O+w=war 3
Oi=war+t=O 4
t=O+w=Colleen -1
Oi=colleen+t=O -1
t=I-LOC+w=Siegel -1
Oi=siegel+t=I-LOC -1
t=I-PER+w=Colleen 3
Oi=colleen+t=I-PER 3
t=I-PER+w=Siegel 3
Oi=siegel+t=I-PER 3
t=O+w=JERUSALEM -5
Oi=jerusalem+t=O -5
t=I-LOC+w=JERUSALEM 3
Oi=jerusalem+t=I-LOC 9
t=I-LOC+w=outgoing -1
Oi=outgoing+t=I-LOC -1
p=JJ+t=I-LOC 1
t=O+w=peace 3
Oi=peace+t=O 2
t=I-LOC+w=current -1
Oi=current+t=I-LOC -1
t=O+w=tensions 0
Oi=tensions+t=O 0
t=O+w=between 3
Oi=between+t=O 3
t=O+w=appeared 0
Oi=appeared+t=O 0
t=O+w=storm 0
Oi=storm+t=O 0
t=O+w=teacup 0
Oi=teacup+t=O 0
t=O+w=outgoing 1
Oi=outgoing+t=O 1
t=O+w=current 3
Oi=current+t=O 3
t=I-LOC+w=Itamar -1
Oi=itamar+t=I-LOC -1
t=O+w=Rabinovich -5
Oi=rabinovich+t=O -5
t=O+w=Israel -5
Oi=israel+t=O -5
t=O+w=ambassador 0
Oi=ambassador+t=O 7
t=O+w=Washington -4
Oi=washington+t=O -5
t=O+w=conducted 0
Oi=conducted+t=O 0
t=O+w=unfruitful 0
Oi=unfruitful+t=O 0
t=O+w=negotiations 1
Oi=negotiations+t=O 1
t=O+w=Radio -1
t=O+w=looked 0
Oi=looked+t=O 0
t=O+w=like 1
Oi=like+t=O 1
t=O+w=Damascus -3
Oi=damascus+t=O -3
t=O+w=wanted 0
Oi=wanted+t=O 0
t=O+w=talk 1
Oi=talk+t=O 3
t=O+w=rather 0
Oi=rather+t=O 0
t=O+w=fight 1
Oi=fight+t=O 1
t=I-PER+w=Itamar 3
Oi=itamar+t=I-PER 3
t=I-PER+w=Rabinovich 6
Oi=rabinovich+t=I-PER 6
t=I-LOC+w=Washington 3
Oi=washington+t=I-LOC 10
t=I-ORG+w=Israel 0
Oi=israel+t=I-ORG 0
t=I-ORG+w=Radio 7
t=I-LOC+w=Damascus 5
Oi=damascus+t=I-LOC 5
t=I-LOC+w=" -2
Oi="+t=I-LOC -2
p="+t=I-LOC -2
t=I-LOC+w=appears -1
Oi=appears+t=I-LOC -1
p=VBZ+t=I-LOC -1
t=I-LOC+w=me -1
Oi=me+t=I-LOC -1
p=PRP+t=I-LOC -3
t=I-LOC+w=Syrian -1
Oi=syrian+t=I-LOC -1
t=O+w=priority 0
Oi=priority+t=O 0
t=I-LOC+w=is -1
Oi=is+t=I-LOC -1
t=O+w=still 2
Oi=still+t=O 2
t=I-LOC+w=negotiate -1
Oi=negotiate+t=I-LOC -1
p=VB+t=I-LOC 0
t=O+w=appears 1
Oi=appears+t=O 1
t=O+w=me 1
Oi=me+t=O 1
t=I-MISC+w=Syrian 7
Oi=syrian+t=I-MISC 7
t=O+w=negotiate 1
Oi=negotiate+t=O 1
t=O+w=Syrians -2
Oi=syrians+t=O -2
t=O+w=confused 1
Oi=confused+t=O 1
t=O+w=they 3
t=O+w=definitely 2
Oi=definitely+t=O 2
t=O+w=tense 2
Oi=tense+t=O 2
t=O+w=assessment 2
Oi=assessment+t=O 2
t=O+w=here 1
Oi=here+t=O 1
t=O+w=essentially 1
Oi=essentially+t=O 1
t=I-MISC+w=Syrians 4
Oi=syrians+t=I-MISC 4
t=O+w=winding 0
Oi=winding+t=O 0
t=O+w=term 2
Oi=term+t=O 6
t=O+w=will 5
Oi=will+t=O -1
t=O+w=replaced 1
Oi=replaced+t=O 1
t=I-ORG+w=Eliahu -1
Oi=eliahu+t=I-ORG -1
t=I-ORG+w=Ben-Elissar -1
Oi=ben-elissar+t=I-ORG -1
t=O+w=Israeli -4
Oi=israeli+t=O -4
t=O+w=envoy 0
Oi=envoy+t=O 4
t=I-LOC+w=Egypt 6
Oi=egypt+t=I-LOC 6
t=O+w=right-wing 2
Oi=right-wing+t=O 2
t=I-LOC+w=Likud -2
Oi=likud+t=I-LOC -2
t=O+w=politician 0
Oi=politician+t=O 0
t=I-PER+w=Eliahu 3
Oi=eliahu+t=I-PER 3
t=I-PER+w=Ben-Elissar 3
Oi=ben-elissar+t=I-PER 3
t=I-MISC+w=Israeli 6
Oi=israeli+t=I-MISC 9
t=I-ORG+w=Likud 5
Oi=likud+t=I-ORG 5
t=I-PER+w=Israel -4
Oi=israel+t=I-PER -4
t=O+w=sent 0
Oi=sent+t=O 0
t=I-PER+w=Syria -1
Oi=syria+t=I-PER -1
t=O+w=message 2
Oi=message+t=O 2
t=O+w=via 0
Oi=via+t=O 0
t=I-PER+w=Washington 4
Oi=washington+t=I-PER 1
t=I-MISC+w=saying -1
Oi=saying+t=I-MISC -1
t=O+w=committed 0
Oi=committed+t=O 0
t=O+w=open 6
Oi=open+t=O 3
t=O+w=without 2
Oi=without+t=O 2
t=O+w=preconditions 0
Oi=preconditions+t=O 0
t=O+w=slammed 0
Oi=slammed+t=O 0
t=O+w=creating 0
Oi=creating+t=O 0
t=O+w=what 2
t=O+w=called 0
Oi=called+t=O 0
t=I-LOC+w=Wednesday -5
Oi=wednesday+t=I-LOC -5
t=O+w=launching 1
Oi=launching+t=O 1
t=O+w=hysterical 1
Oi=hysterical+t=O 1
t=O+w=campaign 2
Oi=campaign+t=O 5
t=O+w=against 3
Oi=against+t=O 1
t=O+w=television 2
Oi=television+t=O 5
t=O+w=reported 1
Oi=reported+t=O 1
t=O+w=recently 2
Oi=recently+t=O 2
t=O+w=test 6
Oi=test+t=O 10
t=O+w=fired 0
Oi=fired+t=O 0
t=O+w=missile 0
Oi=missile+t=O 0
t=O+w=arms 2
Oi=arms+t=O 2
t=O+w=purchases 1
Oi=purchases+t=O 1
t=O+w=defensive 0
Oi=defensive+t=O 0
t=O+w=purposes 0
Oi=purposes+t=O 0
t=O+w=Syrian -6
Oi=syrian+t=O -6
t=I-LOC+w=Hafez -1
Oi=hafez+t=I-LOC -1
t=O+w=al- -3
Oi=al-+t=O -3
t=O+w=Assad -6
Oi=assad+t=O -6
t=O+w=ready 1
Oi=ready+t=O 1
t=O+w=enter 0
Oi=enter+t=O 0
ti=I-ORG+ti-1=I-MISC -7
t=I-ORG+w=Minister -7
Oi=minister+t=I-ORG -7
t=I-ORG+w=David -3
Oi=david+t=I-ORG -3
t=I-LOC+w=Levy -2
Oi=levy+t=I-LOC -2
ti=I-ORG+ti-1=I-LOC -14
t=I-PER+w=Hafez 3
Oi=hafez+t=I-PER 3
t=I-PER+w=al- 3
Oi=al-+t=I-PER 3
t=I-PER+w=Assad 6
Oi=assad+t=I-PER 6
t=O+w=Foreign 6
t=I-PER+w=David 8
Oi=david+t=I-PER 8
t=I-PER+w=Levy 5
Oi=levy+t=I-PER 5
t=O+w=Tension 0
Oi=tension+t=O 1
t=O+w=mounted 1
Oi=mounted+t=O 1
t=O+w=since 3
Oi=since+t=O 3
t=I-PER+w=Israeli -1
Oi=israeli+t=I-PER -2
t=I-PER+w=Prime -3
Oi=prime+t=I-PER -3
t=I-PER+w=Minister -6
Oi=minister+t=I-PER -6
t=I-PER+w=Benjamin 2
Oi=benjamin+t=I-PER 2
t=I-PER+w=Netanyahu 7
Oi=netanyahu+t=I-PER 7
t=O+w=took 1
Oi=took+t=O 1
t=I-PER+w=June -2
Oi=june+t=I-PER -2
t=O+w=vowing 1
Oi=vowing+t=O 1
t=O+w=retain 1
Oi=retain+t=O 1
t=I-PER+w=Golan -2
Oi=golan+t=I-PER -2
t=I-ORG+w=Heights -1
ti=I-ORG+ti-1=I-PER -13
Oi=heights+t=I-ORG -1
t=O+w=captured 1
Oi=captured+t=O 1
t=I-PER+w=Middle -1
Oi=middle+t=I-PER -1
t=I-PER+w=East -5
Oi=east+t=I-PER -5
t=O+w=June 9
Oi=june+t=O 10
t=I-LOC+w=Golan 6
Oi=golan+t=I-LOC 6
t=I-LOC+w=Heights 2
Oi=heights+t=I-LOC 2
p=NNPS+t=I-LOC 1
t=B-LOC+w=Israel 7
ti=B-LOC+ti-1=I-LOC 7
Oi=israel+t=B-LOC 7
ti=O+ti-1=B-LOC 6
t=I-LOC+w=Middle 2
Oi=middle+t=I-LOC 2
t=I-LOC+w=East 4
Oi=east+t=I-LOC 3
t=I-MISC+w=Israeli-Syrian 5
Oi=israeli-syrian+t=I-MISC 5
t=O+w=deadlocked 0
Oi=deadlocked+t=O 0
t=O+w=over 4
Oi=over+t=O 4
t=O+w=Golan -4
Oi=golan+t=O -4
t=O+w=1991 2
Oi=1991+t=O 2
t=O+w=despite 0
Oi=despite+t=O 0
t=O+w=previous 1
Oi=previous+t=O 5
t=O+w=willingness 0
Oi=willingness+t=O 0
t=O+w=concessions 0
Oi=concessions+t=O 0
t=O+w=Peace -1
t=I-MISC+w=last -3
Oi=last+t=I-MISC -4
t=I-LOC+w=February -2
Oi=february+t=I-LOC -2
t=O+w=February 6
Oi=february+t=O 6
t=O+w=voices 0
Oi=voices+t=O 0
t=O+w=coming 2
Oi=coming+t=O 2
t=O+w=out 3
Oi=out+t=O 8
t=O+w=bad 2
Oi=bad+t=O 2
t=O+w=not 4
Oi=not+t=O 4
t=O+w=good 2
Oi=good+t=O 2
t=O+w=full 1
t=O+w=expressions 0
Oi=expressions+t=O 0
t=O+w=declarations 0
Oi=declarations+t=O 0
t=O+w=must 0
Oi=must+t=O 0
t=O+w=worrying 0
Oi=worrying+t=O 0
t=O+w=artificial 2
Oi=artificial+t=O 2
t=O+w=very 2
Oi=very+t=O 2
t=O+w=those 2
Oi=those+t=O 2
t=O+w=spread 0
t=O+w=become 1
Oi=become+t=O 1
t=O+w=prisoners 1
Oi=prisoners+t=O -1
t=O+w=Levy -2
Oi=levy+t=O -2
t=O+w=expect 0
Oi=expect+t=O 0
t=O+w=face 3
Oi=face+t=O 3
t=O+w=answer 1
Oi=answer+t=O 1
t=O+w=our 2
Oi=our+t=O -1
t=O+w=want 2
Oi=want+t=O 2
t=I-LOC+w=God -1
Oi=god+t=I-LOC -1
t=O+w=forbid 0
Oi=forbid+t=O 0
t=I-PER+w=God 4
Oi=god+t=I-PER 4
t=O+w=No -3
t=O+w=one 2
Oi=one+t=O 0
t=O+w=benefits 0
Oi=benefits+t=O 0
t=O+w=wars 0
Oi=wars+t=O 0
t=O+w=Channel -3
Oi=channel+t=O -3
t=O+w=Two -6
t=I-MISC+w=calming -1
Oi=calming+t=I-MISC -1
t=O+w=signal 0
Oi=signal+t=O 0
t=I-ORG+w=Channel 4
Oi=channel+t=I-ORG 4
t=I-ORG+w=Two 4
Oi=two+t=I-ORG 3
t=O+w=calming 1
Oi=calming+t=O 1
t=O+w=source 2
Oi=source+t=O 2
t=O+w=Netanyahu -5
Oi=netanyahu+t=O -5
t=O+w=spokesmen 1
Oi=spokesmen+t=O 1
t=O+w=confirm 0
Oi=confirm+t=O 0
p=NNS+t=I-PER 3
t=O+w=messages 0
Oi=messages+t=O 1
t=O+w=reassure 0
Oi=reassure+t=O 0
t=I-PER+w=Cairo -1
Oi=cairo+t=I-PER -1
t=I-LOC+w=United 4
Oi=united+t=I-LOC 5
t=I-MISC+w=States 3
ti=I-MISC+ti-1=I-LOC -5
Oi=states+t=I-MISC 2
t=I-PER+w=Moscow -2
Oi=moscow+t=I-PER -2
t=I-LOC+w=Cairo 5
Oi=cairo+t=I-LOC 6
t=I-LOC+w=States 9
Oi=states+t=I-LOC 6
t=I-LOC+w=Moscow 5
Oi=moscow+t=I-LOC 8
t=I-MISC+w=Polish 5
Oi=polish+t=I-MISC 10
t=O+w=diplomat 1
Oi=diplomat+t=O 1
t=O+w=denies 0
Oi=denies+t=O 0
t=O+w=nurses 0
Oi=nurses+t=O 0
t=O+w=stranded 1
Oi=stranded+t=O 1
t=I-LOC+w=Libya 3
Oi=libya+t=I-LOC 3
t=I-LOC+w=TUNIS 6
Oi=tunis+t=I-LOC 6
t=O+w=Polish -6
Oi=polish+t=O -7
t=O+w=tabloid 2
Oi=tabloid+t=O 2
t=O+w=refusing 0
Oi=refusing+t=O 0
t=O+w=exit 0
Oi=exit+t=O 0
t=O+w=visas 0
Oi=visas+t=O 0
t=O+w=trying 0
Oi=trying+t=O 0
t=O+w=return 5
Oi=return+t=O 0
t=O+w=home 2
t=O+w=working 1
Oi=working+t=O 4
t=O+w=North -9
Oi=north+t=O -4
t=O+w=African -6
Oi=african+t=O 1
t=O+w=country 3
Oi=country+t=O 2
t=I-MISC+w=North 1
Oi=north+t=I-MISC 0
t=I-MISC+w=African 9
Oi=african+t=I-MISC 7
t=I-MISC+w=" -3
Oi="+t=I-MISC -3
p="+t=I-MISC -3
t=O+w=This 1
t=I-MISC+w=is 3
Oi=is+t=I-MISC 3
t=I-MISC+w=true -1
Oi=true+t=I-MISC -1
t=O+w=true 2
Oi=true+t=O 2
t=O+w=Up 0
t=I-LOC+w=today -1
Oi=today+t=I-LOC -1
p=NN+t=I-LOC -1
t=O+w=knowledge 0
Oi=knowledge+t=O 0
t=I-MISC+w=any -2
Oi=any+t=I-MISC -2
t=O+w=nurse 0
Oi=nurse+t=O 0
t=I-LOC+w=stranded -1
Oi=stranded+t=I-LOC -1
t=O+w=kept 0
Oi=kept+t=O 0
t=I-LOC+w=her -1
Oi=her+t=I-LOC -1
p=PRP$+t=I-LOC 0
t=I-LOC+w=and -2
Oi=and+t=I-LOC -2
p=CC+t=I-LOC 1
t=I-MISC+w=have -1
Oi=have+t=I-MISC -1
p=VBP+t=I-MISC -2
t=I-LOC+w=received -1
Oi=received+t=I-LOC -1
t=I-LOC+w=complaint -1
Oi=complaint+t=I-LOC -1
t=O+w=embassy 3
Oi=embassy+t=O 0
t=O+w=charge 1
Oi=charge+t=O 1
t=I-LOC+w=d'affaires -1
Oi=d'affaires+t=I-LOC -1
t=I-LOC+w=Tripoli 2
Oi=tripoli+t=I-LOC 7
t=I-LOC+w=Tadeusz -1
Oi=tadeusz+t=I-LOC -1
t=I-LOC+w=Awdankiewicz -2
Oi=awdankiewicz+t=I-LOC -2
t=I-LOC+w=telephone -1
Oi=telephone+t=I-LOC -1
t=O+w=today 1
Oi=today+t=O 1
t=O+w=her 2
Oi=her+t=O 3
t=O+w=received 1
Oi=received+t=O 1
t=O+w=complaint 1
Oi=complaint+t=O 1
t=O+w=d'affaires 1
Oi=d'affaires+t=O 1
t=I-PER+w=Tadeusz 1
Oi=tadeusz+t=I-PER 1
t=I-PER+w=Awdankiewicz 3
Oi=awdankiewicz+t=I-PER 3
t=O+w=telephone 1
Oi=telephone+t=O 1
t=O+w=Poland -4
Oi=poland+t=O -4
t=O+w=labour 1
Oi=labour+t=O -2
t=O+w=would 2
Oi=would+t=O 2
t=O+w=send 0
Oi=send+t=O 0
t=O+w=team 3
Oi=team+t=O 4
t=O+w=Libya -2
Oi=libya+t=O -2
t=O+w=investigate 0
Oi=investigate+t=O 0
t=O+w=Awdankiewicz -1
Oi=awdankiewicz+t=O -1
t=O+w=probe 1
Oi=probe+t=O 1
t=O+w=prompted 2
Oi=prompted+t=O 2
t=O+w=complaining 2
Oi=complaining+t=O 2
t=O+w=about 3
Oi=about+t=O 3
t=O+w=work 3
Oi=work+t=O 3
t=O+w=non-payment 0
Oi=non-payment+t=O 0
t=O+w=salaries 0
Oi=salaries+t=O 0
t=I-LOC+w=Poland 4
Oi=poland+t=I-LOC 6
t=O+w=estimated 1
Oi=estimated+t=O 1
t=O+w=800 0
Oi=800+t=O 0
t=O+w=Iranian -3
Oi=iranian+t=O -3
t=O+w=opposition 3
Oi=opposition+t=O 3
t=O+w=leaders 1
Oi=leaders+t=O 1
t=O+w=meet 3
Oi=meet+t=O 3
t=O+w=Baghdad -2
Oi=baghdad+t=O -3
t=I-MISC+w=Iranian 6
Oi=iranian+t=I-MISC 6
t=I-LOC+w=Baghdad 5
Oi=baghdad+t=I-LOC 7
t=I-LOC+w=Hassan -1
Oi=hassan+t=I-LOC -1
t=I-LOC+w=Hafidh -1
Oi=hafidh+t=I-LOC -1
t=I-PER+w=Hassan 4
Oi=hassan+t=I-PER 4
t=I-PER+w=Hafidh 1
Oi=hafidh+t=I-PER 1
t=I-PER+w=BAGHDAD -1
Oi=baghdad+t=I-PER -2
t=I-LOC+w=BAGHDAD 2
t=O+w=An 0
t=O+w=exile 0
Oi=exile+t=O 0
t=O+w=based 2
Oi=based+t=O 2
t=O+w=Iraq -2
Oi=iraq+t=O -4
t=O+w=vowed 1
Oi=vowed+t=O 1
t=O+w=extend 0
Oi=extend+t=O 0
t=O+w=Iran -3
Oi=iran+t=O -3
t=O+w=Kurdish -5
Oi=kurdish+t=O -5
t=O+w=rebels 3
Oi=rebels+t=O 3
t=O+w=attacked 0
Oi=attacked+t=O 0
t=O+w=troops 2
Oi=troops+t=O 2
t=O+w=deep 0
Oi=deep+t=O 0
t=O+w=inside 0
Oi=inside+t=O 0
t=I-LOC+w=Iraq 6
Oi=iraq+t=I-LOC 8
t=I-LOC+w=Iran 4
Oi=iran+t=I-LOC 4
t=I-MISC+w=Kurdish 5
Oi=kurdish+t=I-MISC 5
t=I-LOC+w=Mujahideen -2
Oi=mujahideen+t=I-LOC -2
t=I-LOC+w=Khalq -1
Oi=khalq+t=I-LOC -1
t=O+w=statement 2
Oi=statement+t=O 8
t=O+w=leader 5
Oi=leader+t=O 5
t=I-LOC+w=Massoud -2
Oi=massoud+t=I-LOC -2
t=I-LOC+w=Rajavi -1
Oi=rajavi+t=I-LOC -1
t=O+w=met 2
Oi=met+t=O 2
t=I-LOC+w=Secretary-General -1
Oi=secretary-general+t=I-LOC -1
t=I-LOC+w=Kurdistan 0
Oi=kurdistan+t=I-LOC 0
t=I-LOC+w=Democratic -2
Oi=democratic+t=I-LOC -2
t=I-LOC+w=Party -3
Oi=party+t=I-LOC -3
t=I-LOC+w=KDPI -1
Oi=kdpi+t=I-LOC -1
t=I-LOC+w=Rastegar -1
Oi=rastegar+t=I-LOC -1
t=O+w=voiced 0
Oi=voiced+t=O 0
t=O+w=rebel 2
Oi=rebel+t=O 2
t=I-MISC+w=Kurds 4
Oi=kurds+t=I-MISC 4
t=I-ORG+w=Mujahideen 3
Oi=mujahideen+t=I-ORG 3
t=I-ORG+w=Khalq 3
Oi=khalq+t=I-ORG 3
t=I-PER+w=Massoud 4
Oi=massoud+t=I-PER 4
t=I-PER+w=Rajavi -1
Oi=rajavi+t=I-PER -1
t=O+w=Secretary-General 5
Oi=secretary-general+t=O 7
t=I-ORG+w=Kurdistan 4
Oi=kurdistan+t=I-ORG 4
t=I-ORG+w=Democratic 2
Oi=democratic+t=I-ORG 1
t=I-ORG+w=Party 14
Oi=party+t=I-ORG 6
t=I-ORG+w=of 1
Oi=of+t=I-ORG -2
t=I-ORG+w=Iran 1
Oi=iran+t=I-ORG 1
t=I-ORG+w=KDPI 4
Oi=kdpi+t=I-ORG 4
t=I-PER+w=Rastegar 1
Oi=rastegar+t=I-PER 1
t=I-ORG+w=Rajavi -1
Oi=rajavi+t=I-ORG -1
t=O+w=emphasised 0
Oi=emphasised+t=O 0
t=O+w=Resistance -7
Oi=resistance+t=O -5
t=O+w=continue 1
Oi=continue+t=O 5
t=O+w=stand 0
Oi=stand+t=O 0
t=O+w=side 2
Oi=side+t=O 2
t=O+w=compatriots 0
Oi=compatriots+t=O 0
t=O+w=resistance 2
t=O+w=movement 2
Oi=movement+t=O 1
t=I-ORG+w=Iranian -6
Oi=iranian+t=I-ORG -6
t=I-MISC+w=Rajavi 4
Oi=rajavi+t=I-MISC 4
t=I-ORG+w=Resistance 9
Oi=resistance+t=I-ORG 7
t=I-LOC+w=Iranian 4
Oi=iranian+t=I-LOC 4
t=O+w=signals 0
Oi=signals+t=O 0
t=I-MISC+w=new -2
Oi=new+t=I-MISC 1
t=O+w=level 2
Oi=level+t=O 2
t=O+w=cooperation 2
Oi=cooperation+t=O 0
t=I-PER+w=Iranian -1
Oi=iranian+t=I-PER -1
t=I-PER+w=Kurdish -1
Oi=kurdish+t=I-PER -1
t=O+w=oppositions 0
Oi=oppositions+t=O 0
t=I-PER+w=Iran -2
Oi=iran+t=I-PER -2
t=O+w=heavily 1
Oi=heavily+t=O 1
t=O+w=bombarded 0
Oi=bombarded+t=O 0
t=O+w=targets 0
Oi=targets+t=O 0
t=I-MISC+w=northern -2
Oi=northern+t=I-MISC -4
t=I-PER+w=Iraq -2
Oi=iraq+t=I-PER -2
t=I-MISC+w=July -2
Oi=july+t=I-MISC -2
t=O+w=pursuit 1
Oi=pursuit+t=O 1
t=O+w=guerrillas 1
Oi=guerrillas+t=O 1
t=I-MISC+w=Iraqi 3
Oi=iraqi+t=I-MISC 3
t=O+w=areas 1
Oi=areas+t=O 1
t=O+w=outside 2
Oi=outside+t=O 2
t=O+w=control 2
Oi=control+t=O 2
t=I-ORG+w=Baghdad -2
Oi=baghdad+t=I-ORG -2
t=O+w=northern 6
Oi=northern+t=O 0
t=O+w=bordering 0
Oi=bordering+t=O 0
t=O+w=Iraqi -8
Oi=iraqi+t=O -8
t=I-ORG+w=Patriotic 4
Oi=patriotic+t=I-ORG 4
t=O+w=Kurdistan -2
Oi=kurdistan+t=O -2
t=O+w=PUK -2
Oi=puk+t=O -2
t=I-ORG+w=Iraqi 2
Oi=iraqi+t=I-ORG 2
t=I-ORG+w=Kurdish 2
Oi=kurdish+t=I-ORG 2
t=I-ORG+w=PUK 8
Oi=puk+t=I-ORG 8
t=I-ORG+w=and 1
Oi=and+t=I-ORG 2
p=CC+t=I-ORG 0
t=I-ORG+w=Iraq -2
Oi=iraq+t=I-ORG -2
t=I-ORG+w=KDP 7
Oi=kdp+t=I-ORG 7
t=I-ORG+w=) 1
Oi=)+t=I-ORG 1
p=)+t=I-ORG 0
t=I-ORG+w=two -1
t=I-ORG+w=main -2
Oi=main+t=I-ORG -4
t=I-ORG+w=factions -1
Oi=factions+t=I-ORG -1
t=I-ORG+w=, -1
Oi=,+t=I-ORG -1
p=,+t=I-ORG -2
t=I-ORG+w=have -2
Oi=have+t=I-ORG -4
t=I-ORG+w=had -2
Oi=had+t=I-ORG -2
p=VBD+t=I-ORG -5
t=I-ORG+w=northern -2
Oi=northern+t=I-ORG 3
t=I-ORG+w=under -1
Oi=under+t=I-ORG -1
t=I-ORG+w=their -1
Oi=their+t=I-ORG -4
p=PRP$+t=I-ORG -6
t=I-ORG+w=control -2
Oi=control+t=I-ORG 1
t=I-ORG+w=since -2
Oi=since+t=I-ORG -2
t=I-ORG+w=forces -1
Oi=forces+t=I-ORG 2
t=I-ORG+w=were -2
Oi=were+t=I-ORG -2
t=I-ORG+w=ousted -1
Oi=ousted+t=I-ORG -1
p=VBN+t=I-ORG 1
t=I-ORG+w=from -3
Oi=from+t=I-ORG -3
t=I-ORG+w=Kuwait -1
Oi=kuwait+t=I-ORG -1
t=I-ORG+w=1991 -1
Oi=1991+t=I-ORG -1
t=I-ORG+w=Gulf -5
Oi=gulf+t=I-ORG -6
t=I-ORG+w=War -2
Oi=war+t=I-ORG -2
t=I-ORG+w=. -1
Oi=.+t=I-ORG -1
p=.+t=I-ORG -1
t=O+w=main 3
Oi=main+t=O 7
t=O+w=factions 1
Oi=factions+t=O 1
t=O+w=forces 3
Oi=forces+t=O 1
t=O+w=ousted 1
Oi=ousted+t=O 1
t=I-LOC+w=Kuwait 4
Oi=kuwait+t=I-LOC 4
t=I-MISC+w=Gulf 5
Oi=gulf+t=I-MISC 5
t=I-MISC+w=War 6
Oi=war+t=I-MISC 4
t=O+w=Clashes 0
Oi=clashes+t=O 0
t=O+w=parties 1
Oi=parties+t=O 1
t=O+w=broke 0
Oi=broke+t=O 0
t=O+w=weekend 2
Oi=weekend+t=O 5
t=O+w=most 2
Oi=most+t=O 2
p=RBS+t=O 1
t=O+w=serious 4
Oi=serious+t=O 4
t=O+w=fighting 1
Oi=fighting+t=O 1
t=O+w=U.S.-sponsored -4
Oi=u.s.-sponsored+t=O -4
t=O+w=ceasefire 1
Oi=ceasefire+t=O 1
t=I-MISC+w=U.S.-sponsored 4
Oi=u.s.-sponsored+t=I-MISC 4
t=I-MISC+w=Khalq -1
Oi=khalq+t=I-MISC -1
t=O+w=shelling 1
Oi=shelling+t=O 1
t=O+w=KDP -3
Oi=kdp+t=O -3
t=O+w=positions 0
Oi=positions+t=O 4
t=O+w=Qasri -1
Oi=qasri+t=O -1
t=O+w=region 2
Oi=region+t=O 2
t=O+w=Suleimaniya -1
Oi=suleimaniya+t=O -1
t=O+w=near 7
Oi=near+t=O -1
t=O+w=border 2
Oi=border+t=O 2
t=O+w=days 3
Oi=days+t=O 3
t=I-LOC+w=Qasri 3
Oi=qasri+t=I-LOC 3
t=I-LOC+w=Suleimaniya 3
Oi=suleimaniya+t=I-LOC 3
t=O+w=Kurds -2
Oi=kurds+t=O -2
t=O+w=killed 1
Oi=killed+t=O 1
t=O+w=wounded 0
Oi=wounded+t=O 0
t=O+w=attack 1
Oi=attack+t=O 1
t=O+w=Both 2
Oi=both+t=O 7
t=I-ORG+w=Turkey -2
Oi=turkey+t=I-ORG -2
t=O+w=mount 0
Oi=mount+t=O 0
t=O+w=air 1
Oi=air+t=O 3
t=O+w=land 0
Oi=land+t=O -1
t=O+w=strikes 0
Oi=strikes+t=O 0
ti=I-LOC+ti-1=I-MISC -4
t=I-MISC+w=own -3
Oi=own+t=I-MISC -3
t=I-LOC+w=Turkey 7
Oi=turkey+t=I-LOC 7
t=O+w=own 4
Oi=own+t=O 4
t=O+w=U.S.-led -4
Oi=u.s.-led+t=O -4
t=O+w=force 1
t=I-MISC+w=southern -3
Oi=southern+t=I-MISC 2
t=O+w=protects 0
Oi=protects+t=O 0
t=O+w=possible 3
Oi=possible+t=O 3
t=O+w=attacks 1
Oi=attacks+t=O 1
t=I-MISC+w=U.S.-led 5
Oi=u.s.-led+t=I-MISC 5
t=O+w=southern 7
Oi=southern+t=O 0
t=I-MISC+w=Saudi 8
Oi=saudi+t=I-MISC 8
t=I-MISC+w=riyal -1
Oi=riyal+t=I-MISC -1
t=O+w=rates 2
Oi=rates+t=O 2
t=O+w=steady 2
Oi=steady+t=O 2
t=I-MISC+w=quiet -2
Oi=quiet+t=I-MISC -2
t=O+w=summer 1
Oi=summer+t=O 1
t=O+w=trade 4
Oi=trade+t=O 6
t=O+w=riyal 1
Oi=riyal+t=O 1
t=O+w=quiet 2
Oi=quiet+t=O 2
t=I-LOC+w=MANAMA 3
Oi=manama+t=I-LOC 3
t=O+w=spot 1
Oi=spot+t=O 4
t=O+w=Saudi -7
Oi=saudi+t=O -7
t=O+w=dollar 1
Oi=dollar+t=O 1
t=O+w=interbank 0
Oi=interbank+t=O -1
t=O+w=deposit 0
Oi=deposit+t=O 0
t=O+w=mainly 2
Oi=mainly+t=O 2
t=O+w=dealers 0
Oi=dealers+t=O 0
t=O+w=kingdom 2
Oi=kingdom+t=O 1
t=O+w=There 1
t=O+w=changes 0
Oi=changes+t=O 0
t=O+w=market 2
Oi=market+t=O 5
t=O+w=holidays 0
Oi=holidays+t=O 0
t=O+w=dealer 0
Oi=dealer+t=O 0
t=O+w=3.7504 0
Oi=3.7504+t=O 0
t=O+w=06 0
Oi=06+t=O 0
t=I-MISC+w=One-month 4
Oi=one-month+t=I-MISC 4
t=O+w=deposits 0
Oi=deposits+t=O 0
t=O+w=5-1/2 0
Oi=5-1/2+t=O 0
t=O+w=3/8 0
Oi=3/8+t=O 0
t=O+w=three 6
Oi=three+t=O 6
t=O+w=months 1
Oi=months+t=O 4
t=O+w=5-5/8 0
Oi=5-5/8+t=O 0
t=O+w=1/2 0
Oi=1/2+t=O 0
t=O+w=six 1
Oi=six+t=O 1
t=O+w=5-3/4 0
Oi=5-3/4+t=O 0
t=O+w=5/8 0
Oi=5/8+t=O 0
t=I-MISC+w=One-year 4
Oi=one-year+t=I-MISC 4
t=O+w=funds 1
Oi=funds+t=O 1
t=O+w=5-7/8 2
Oi=5-7/8+t=O 2
t=O+w=approves 0
Oi=approves+t=O 4
t=I-LOC+w=Arafat -4
Oi=arafat+t=I-LOC -4
t=O+w=flight 1
Oi=flight+t=O 1
t=I-LOC+w=West 4
Oi=west+t=I-LOC 6
t=I-LOC+w=Bank 1
Oi=bank+t=I-LOC 0
t=I-PER+w=Arafat 6
Oi=arafat+t=I-PER 6
t=O+w=Palestinian -6
Oi=palestinian+t=O -6
t=I-LOC+w=President -3
Oi=president+t=I-LOC -3
t=I-PER+w=Yasser 2
Oi=yasser+t=I-PER 2
t=O+w=permission 1
Oi=permission+t=O 1
t=I-MISC+w=Thursday -2
Oi=thursday+t=I-MISC -3
t=O+w=fly 1
Oi=fly+t=O 1
t=O+w=territory 0
Oi=territory+t=O 0
t=O+w=ending 0
Oi=ending+t=O 0
t=O+w=brief 2
Oi=brief+t=O 2
t=O+w=Israeli-PLO -4
Oi=israeli-plo+t=O -4
t=O+w=crisis 0
Oi=crisis+t=O 0
t=O+w=adviser 3
Oi=adviser+t=O 3
t=I-MISC+w=Palestinian 6
Oi=palestinian+t=I-MISC 6
t=I-MISC+w=Israeli-PLO 6
Oi=israeli-plo+t=I-MISC 6
t=O+w=problem 1
Oi=problem+t=O 1
t=O+w=president 0
t=O+w=aircraft 0
Oi=aircraft+t=O 4
t=O+w=pass 0
Oi=pass+t=O 0
t=O+w=airspace 0
Oi=airspace+t=O 0
t=O+w=expected 2
Oi=expected+t=O 2
t=O+w=travel 1
Oi=travel+t=O 1
t=I-MISC+w=West 3
Oi=west+t=I-MISC 3
t=I-MISC+w=Bank -3
Oi=bank+t=I-MISC -4
t=O+w=before 6
Oi=before+t=O 6
t=I-MISC+w=Monday -2
Oi=monday+t=I-MISC -2
t=I-PER+w=Nabil 1
Oi=nabil+t=I-PER 1
t=I-PER+w=Abu 3
Oi=abu+t=I-PER 3
t=I-PER+w=Rdainah 2
Oi=rdainah+t=I-PER 2
t=O+w=Monday 7
Oi=monday+t=O 9
t=O+w=scheduled 0
Oi=scheduled+t=O 0
t=I-MISC+w=former -2
Oi=former+t=I-MISC -3
t=O+w=prime 0
t=O+w=minister 0
t=I-LOC+w=Shimon -1
Oi=shimon+t=I-LOC -1
t=I-LOC+w=Peres -2
Oi=peres+t=I-LOC -2
t=O+w=town 4
Oi=town+t=O 2
t=I-LOC+w=Ramallah 5
Oi=ramallah+t=I-LOC 6
t=O+w=venue 1
Oi=venue+t=O 1
t=O+w=changed 0
Oi=changed+t=O 0
t=I-LOC+w=Gaza 4
Oi=gaza+t=I-LOC 5
t=O+w=clearance 0
Oi=clearance+t=O 0
t=O+w=helicopters 0
Oi=helicopters+t=O 0
t=I-PER+w=Shimon 1
Oi=shimon+t=I-PER 1
t=I-PER+w=Peres 4
Oi=peres+t=I-PER 4
t=O+w=stop 1
Oi=stop+t=O 1
t=I-PER+w=Ramallah -2
Oi=ramallah+t=I-PER -2
t=O+w=keeping 0
Oi=keeping+t=O 0
t=O+w=grounded 0
Oi=grounded+t=O 0
t=O+w=subsequently 1
Oi=subsequently+t=O 1
t=O+w=cancelled 0
Oi=cancelled+t=O 0
t=O+w=PLO -3
Oi=plo+t=O -3
t=O+w=civilian 2
Oi=civilian+t=O 2
t=O+w=affairs -1
Oi=affairs+t=O 6
t=I-PER+w=Allenby 1
Oi=allenby+t=I-PER 1
t=I-PER+w=Bridge -4
Oi=bridge+t=I-PER -4
t=O+w=crossing 0
Oi=crossing+t=O 0
t=O+w=Jordan -3
Oi=jordan+t=O -3
t=I-PER+w=West -2
Oi=west+t=I-PER -4
t=I-PER+w=Bank -4
Oi=bank+t=I-PER -4
t=I-ORG+w=PLO 8
Oi=plo+t=I-ORG 8
t=I-LOC+w=Allenby 2
Oi=allenby+t=I-LOC 2
t=I-LOC+w=Bridge 3
Oi=bridge+t=I-LOC 3
t=I-LOC+w=Jordan 3
Oi=jordan+t=I-LOC 1
t=I-LOC+w=Abu 1
Oi=abu+t=I-LOC 1
t=I-LOC+w=Rdainah -2
Oi=rdainah+t=I-LOC -2
t=O+w=decided 0
Oi=decided+t=O 0
t=O+w=flying 0
Oi=flying+t=O 0
t=O+w=lifted 0
Oi=lifted+t=O 0
t=I-MISC+w=busy -1
Oi=busy+t=I-MISC -1
t=O+w=schedule 0
Oi=schedule+t=O 6
t=I-MISC+w=free -2
Oi=free+t=I-MISC -4
t=I-LOC+w=Monday -2
Oi=monday+t=I-LOC -2
t=O+w=busy 1
Oi=busy+t=O 1
t=O+w=free 0
Oi=free+t=O 4
t=O+w=Arafat -2
Oi=arafat+t=O -2
t=O+w=Peres -2
Oi=peres+t=O -2
t=O+w=Gaza -1
Oi=gaza+t=O -1
t=O+w=Palestinians -2
Oi=palestinians+t=O -2
t=O+w=barred 0
Oi=barred+t=O 0
t=I-MISC+w=Palestinians 7
Oi=palestinians+t=I-MISC 7
t=I-LOC+w=Erez 1
Oi=erez+t=I-LOC 1
t=O+w=checkpoint 0
Oi=checkpoint+t=O 0
t=O+w=planned 1
Oi=planned+t=O 1
t=O+w=overflying 0
Oi=overflying+t=O 0
t=O+w=helicopter 1
Oi=helicopter+t=O 1
t=O+w=attempt 0
Oi=attempt+t=O 0
t=O+w=bar 0
Oi=bar+t=O 0
t=I-LOC+w=Israeli -1
Oi=israeli+t=I-LOC -2
t=I-LOC+w=Prime -2
Oi=prime+t=I-LOC -2
t=I-ORG+w=Benjamin -1
Oi=benjamin+t=I-ORG -1
ti=I-PER+ti-1=I-ORG -1
t=O+w=defeated 0
Oi=defeated+t=O 0
t=I-LOC+w=May -2
Oi=may+t=I-LOC -3
t=O+w=undermine 0
Oi=undermine+t=O 0
t=O+w=authority 1
Oi=authority+t=O -1
t=O+w=conduct 0
Oi=conduct+t=O 0
t=O+w=May 2
Oi=may+t=O 9
t=I-PER+w=Afghan -1
Oi=afghan+t=I-PER -1
t=I-PER+w=UAE -1
Oi=uae+t=I-PER -1
t=I-PER+w=Taleban -1
Oi=taleban+t=I-PER -1
t=O+w=guards 0
Oi=guards+t=O 0
t=I-MISC+w=Afghan 9
Oi=afghan+t=I-MISC 9
t=I-LOC+w=UAE 5
Oi=uae+t=I-LOC 5
t=I-MISC+w=Taleban 5
Oi=taleban+t=I-MISC 5
t=I-PER+w=Hilary 2
Oi=hilary+t=I-PER 2
t=I-PER+w=Gush 2
Oi=gush+t=I-PER 2
t=I-MISC+w=DUBAI -1
Oi=dubai+t=I-MISC -1
t=I-LOC+w=DUBAI 3
Oi=dubai+t=I-LOC 5
t=O+w=Three 0
t=B-LOC+w=Arab -1
Oi=arab+t=B-LOC -1
t=I-LOC+w=Emirates 4
ti=I-LOC+ti-1=B-LOC 4
Oi=emirates+t=I-LOC 4
t=I-MISC+w=Russian 5
Oi=russian+t=I-MISC 9
t=O+w=hostages 1
Oi=hostages+t=O 1
t=O+w=escaped 0
Oi=escaped+t=O 0
t=O+w=militia 0
Oi=militia+t=O 0
t=I-MISC+w=Afghanistan -1
Oi=afghanistan+t=I-MISC -1
t=I-MISC+w=few -4
Oi=few+t=I-MISC -4
t=I-MISC+w=Abu -1
Oi=abu+t=I-MISC -1
t=I-LOC+w=Dhabi 4
Oi=dhabi+t=I-LOC 4
t=I-LOC+w=Arab 2
Oi=arab+t=I-LOC 2
t=I-LOC+w=Afghanistan 5
Oi=afghanistan+t=I-LOC 5
t=O+w=few 5
Oi=few+t=O 5
t=O+w=Our -3
t=O+w=touch 1
Oi=touch+t=O 1
t=O+w=Their 0
t=O+w=issuing 0
Oi=issuing+t=O 0
t=O+w=them 1
Oi=them+t=O 1
t=O+w=documents 1
Oi=documents+t=O 1
t=O+w=homeland 0
Oi=homeland+t=O 0
t=O+w=objection 0
Oi=objection+t=O 0
t=O+w=added 1
Oi=added+t=O 1
t=I-LOC+w=Islamic -1
Oi=islamic+t=I-LOC -1
t=I-LOC+w=Taleban -3
Oi=taleban+t=I-LOC -3
t=O+w=overpowered 0
Oi=overpowered+t=O 0
t=O+w=seven 2
Oi=seven+t=O -1
t=O+w=Russian -5
Oi=russian+t=O -5
t=O+w=aircrew 0
Oi=aircrew+t=O 0
t=I-LOC+w=Sharjah 2
Oi=sharjah+t=I-LOC 2
t=I-LOC+w=Friday -3
Oi=friday+t=I-LOC -3
t=O+w=board 3
Oi=board+t=O 1
t=O+w=captivity 0
Oi=captivity+t=O 0
t=O+w=Taleban -1
Oi=taleban+t=O -1
t=I-LOC+w=Kandahar 3
Oi=kandahar+t=I-LOC 3
t=I-MISC+w=Islamic 4
Oi=islamic+t=I-MISC 4
t=O+w=Friday 10
Oi=friday+t=O 12
t=I-MISC+w=UAE -3
Oi=uae+t=I-MISC -3
t=O+w=hand 0
Oi=hand+t=O 2
t=I-MISC+w=International 4
Oi=international+t=I-MISC 5
t=O+w=Red -3
Oi=red+t=O -2
t=I-MISC+w=Crescent -1
Oi=crescent+t=I-MISC -1
t=O+w=possibly 0
Oi=possibly+t=O 0
t=I-MISC+w=Tuesday -2
Oi=tuesday+t=I-MISC -2
t=I-ORG+w=Red 2
Oi=red+t=I-ORG 1
t=I-ORG+w=Crescent 6
Oi=crescent+t=I-ORG 6
t=O+w=Tuesday 9
Oi=tuesday+t=O 11
t=O+w=silent 1
Oi=silent+t=O 1
t=O+w=When 0
Oi=when+t=O 2
t=O+w=asked 0
Oi=asked+t=O 5
t=O+w=back 3
Oi=back+t=O 6
t=O+w=Kandahar -2
Oi=kandahar+t=O -2
t=O+w=Afghan -2
Oi=afghan+t=O -2
t=O+w=capital 2
Oi=capital+t=O 3
t=O+w=Kabul -1
Oi=kabul+t=O -5
t=O+w=That 0
t=I-LOC+w=Kabul 2
Oi=kabul+t=I-LOC 6
t=O+w=headquarters 2
Oi=headquarters+t=O 2
t=O+w=controlled 0
Oi=controlled+t=O 0
t=I-LOC+w=Burhanuddin -1
Oi=burhanuddin+t=I-LOC -1
t=I-LOC+w=Rabbani -2
Oi=rabbani+t=I-LOC -2
t=O+w=overthrow 0
Oi=overthrow+t=O 0
t=I-PER+w=Burhanuddin 1
Oi=burhanuddin+t=I-PER 1
t=I-PER+w=Rabbani 5
Oi=rabbani+t=I-PER 5
t=O+w=men 2
Oi=men+t=O 1
t=O+w=20s 0
Oi=20s+t=O 0
t=O+w=currently 0
Oi=currently+t=O 0
t=I-ORG+w=Dhabi -1
Oi=dhabi+t=I-ORG -1
t=O+w=did 1
Oi=did+t=O 1
t=O+w=elaborate 0
Oi=elaborate+t=O 0
t=I-MISC+w=Russians 3
Oi=russians+t=I-MISC 3
t=I-MISC+w=Aerostan -2
Oi=aerostan+t=I-MISC -2
t=O+w=firm 3
Oi=firm+t=O 3
t=O+w=republic 3
Oi=republic+t=O 0
t=I-LOC+w=Tatarstan 1
Oi=tatarstan+t=I-LOC 1
t=O+w=hostage 2
Oi=hostage+t=O 2
t=I-LOC+w=MiG-19 -1
Oi=mig-19+t=I-LOC -1
t=O+w=fighter 0
Oi=fighter+t=O 0
t=O+w=forced 1
Oi=forced+t=O 3
t=O+w=cargo 1
Oi=cargo+t=O 1
t=O+w=plane 1
Oi=plane+t=O 2
t=I-LOC+w=August -2
Oi=august+t=I-LOC -2
t=I-ORG+w=Aerostan 6
Oi=aerostan+t=I-ORG 6
t=B-MISC+w=MiG-19 4
ti=B-MISC+ti-1=I-MISC 12
Oi=mig-19+t=B-MISC 4
p=NNP+t=B-MISC -3
ti=O+ti-1=B-MISC 7
t=O+w=August 8
Oi=august+t=O 10
t=O+w=shipment 1
Oi=shipment+t=O 1
t=O+w=ammunition 1
Oi=ammunition+t=O 1
t=I-ORG+w=Albania -3
Oi=albania+t=I-ORG -3
t=O+w=evidence 0
Oi=evidence+t=O 0
t=I-MISC+w=military -1
Oi=military+t=I-MISC -1
t=O+w=Rabbani -3
Oi=rabbani+t=O -3
t=I-LOC+w=Albania 6
Oi=albania+t=I-LOC 6
t=O+w=military 3
Oi=military+t=O 2
t=O+w=crew 1
Oi=crew+t=O 1
t=O+w=nationality 0
Oi=nationality+t=O 0
t=I-MISC+w=coincidental -1
Oi=coincidental+t=I-MISC -1
t=O+w=coincidental 1
Oi=coincidental+t=O 1
t=I-MISC+w=Numerous -2
Oi=numerous+t=I-MISC -2
t=O+w=diplomatic 3
Oi=diplomatic+t=O 3
t=O+w=attempts 0
Oi=attempts+t=O 0
t=O+w=failed 1
Oi=failed+t=O 1
t=O+w=Numerous 3
Oi=numerous+t=O 3
t=O+w=Russians -1
Oi=russians+t=O -1
t=O+w=armed 1
Oi=armed+t=O 4
t=I-LOC+w=Kalashnikov -2
Oi=kalashnikov+t=I-LOC -2
t=O+w=automatic 2
Oi=automatic+t=O 2
t=O+w=rifles 0
Oi=rifles+t=O 0
t=O+w=doing 2
Oi=doing+t=O 2
t=O+w=regular 1
Oi=regular+t=O 1
t=O+w=maintenance 0
Oi=maintenance+t=O 0
t=I-PER+w=Ilyushin -1
Oi=ilyushin+t=I-PER -1
t=I-PER+w=76 -1
Oi=76+t=I-PER -1
t=O+w=left 1
Oi=left+t=O 5
t=I-LOC+w=Sunday -2
Oi=sunday+t=I-LOC -2
t=I-MISC+w=Kalashnikov 7
Oi=kalashnikov+t=I-MISC 7
t=I-MISC+w=Ilyushin 3
Oi=ilyushin+t=I-MISC 3
t=I-MISC+w=76 2
Oi=76+t=I-MISC 2
t=O+w=Sunday 6
Oi=sunday+t=O 8
t=I-ORG+w=Saddam -2
Oi=saddam+t=I-ORG -2
t=O+w=meets 2
Oi=meets+t=O 2
t=I-ORG+w=Russia -2
Oi=russia+t=I-ORG -2
t=I-ORG+w=Zhirinovsky -1
Oi=zhirinovsky+t=I-ORG -1
t=I-PER+w=Saddam 4
Oi=saddam+t=I-PER 4
t=I-LOC+w=Russia 8
Oi=russia+t=I-LOC 9
t=I-PER+w=Zhirinovsky 4
Oi=zhirinovsky+t=I-PER 4
t=I-PER+w=Hussein 4
Oi=hussein+t=I-PER 4
t=O+w=ultra-nationalist 0
Oi=ultra-nationalist+t=O 0
t=I-PER+w=Vladimir 2
Oi=vladimir+t=I-PER 2
t=O+w=maintain 0
Oi=maintain+t=O 0
t=O+w=friendship 0
Oi=friendship+t=O 0
t=O+w=newspapers 0
Oi=newspapers+t=O 4
t=O+w=stressed 0
Oi=stressed+t=O 0
t=O+w=during 2
Oi=during+t=O 2
t=O+w=keenness 0
Oi=keenness+t=O 0
t=O+w=papers 0
Oi=papers+t=O 0
t=O+w=Liberal -6
Oi=liberal+t=O -2
t=O+w=Democratic -9
Oi=democratic+t=O -3
t=I-LOC+w=Russian 2
Oi=russian+t=I-LOC 2
t=O+w=Duma -1
Oi=duma+t=O -1
t=O+w=parliament 0
Oi=parliament+t=O 5
t=O+w=calling 0
Oi=calling+t=O 0
t=O+w=immediate 1
Oi=immediate+t=O 2
t=O+w=lifting 0
Oi=lifting+t=O 0
t=O+w=embargo 1
Oi=embargo+t=O 1
t=O+w=imposed 0
Oi=imposed+t=O 0
t=O+w=1990 -2
Oi=1990+t=O -2
t=O+w=invasion 0
Oi=invasion+t=O 0
t=I-ORG+w=Liberal 10
Oi=liberal+t=I-ORG 7
t=I-ORG+w=party -2
t=I-ORG+w=Duma 6
Oi=duma+t=I-ORG 6
t=I-PER+w=Tuesday -3
Oi=tuesday+t=I-PER -4
t=O+w=press 1
Oi=press+t=O 5
t=O+w=help 2
Oi=help+t=O 2
t=I-MISC+w=U.N. -1
Oi=u.n.+t=I-MISC -1
t=O+w=sanctions 1
Oi=sanctions+t=O 1
t=O+w=blamed 2
Oi=blamed+t=O 2
t=O+w=delaying 1
Oi=delaying+t=O 1
t=O+w=establishment 0
Oi=establishment+t=O 0
t=I-MISC+w=good -1
Oi=good+t=I-MISC -1
t=O+w=ties 0
Oi=ties+t=O 4
t=I-ORG+w=U.N. 8
Oi=u.n.+t=I-ORG 8
t=O+w=namely 0
Oi=namely+t=O 0
t=O+w=economic 7
Oi=economic+t=O 0
t=O+w=resume 0
Oi=resume+t=O 0
t=O+w=visited 0
Oi=visited+t=O 0
t=O+w=twice 1
Oi=twice+t=O 1
t=O+w=Last 1
t=I-LOC+w=October -2
Oi=october+t=I-LOC -2
t=O+w=invited 0
Oi=invited+t=O 0
t=O+w=attend 0
Oi=attend+t=O 0
t=O+w=referendum 0
Oi=referendum+t=O 0
t=O+w=presidency 1
Oi=presidency+t=O 2
t=O+w=extended 0
Oi=extended+t=O 0
t=O+w=years 2
Oi=years+t=O 2
t=O+w=October 6
Oi=october+t=O 6
t=O+w=PRESS 2
t=O+w=DIGEST 9
Oi=digest+t=O 9
t=O+w=22 0
Oi=22+t=O 0
t=O+w=These 1
Oi=these+t=O 3
t=O+w=leading 2
Oi=leading+t=O 8
t=O+w=stories 2
Oi=stories+t=O 2
t=O+w=verified 1
Oi=verified+t=O 1
t=O+w=these 2
t=O+w=does 1
Oi=does+t=O 1
t=O+w=vouch 1
Oi=vouch+t=O 1
t=O+w=accuracy 1
Oi=accuracy+t=O 1
t=O+w=THAWRA -8
Oi=thawra+t=O -8
t=I-ORG+w=THAWRA 8
Oi=thawra+t=I-ORG 8
t=O+w=Saddam -1
Oi=saddam+t=O -1
t=O+w=Hussein -1
Oi=hussein+t=O -1
t=O+w=liberal 4
t=I-MISC+w=democratic -5
Oi=democratic+t=I-MISC 6
t=O+w=Vladimir -1
Oi=vladimir+t=O -1
t=O+w=Zhirinovsky -1
Oi=zhirinovsky+t=O -1
t=O+w=democratic 6
t=I-ORG+w=- -2
Oi=-+t=I-ORG -2
p=:+t=I-ORG -9
t=O+w=Turkish -5
Oi=turkish+t=O -5
t=I-MISC+w=foreign -1
Oi=foreign+t=I-MISC -4
t=I-PER+w=Turkey -2
Oi=turkey+t=I-PER -2
t=O+w=part 2
Oi=part+t=O 2
t=I-PER+w=Baghdad -1
t=I-MISC+w=fair -3
Oi=fair+t=I-MISC 4
t=I-PER+w=November -2
Oi=november+t=I-PER -2
t=I-MISC+w=Turkish 6
Oi=turkish+t=I-MISC 10
t=O+w=fair 3
Oi=fair+t=O 1
t=O+w=November 8
Oi=november+t=O 8
t=I-LOC+w=IRAQ 2
t=O+w=shipload 0
Oi=shipload+t=O 0
t=O+w=12 1
Oi=12+t=O 1
t=O+w=rice 0
Oi=rice+t=O 8
t=O+w=arrives 0
Oi=arrives+t=O 0
t=O+w=Umm -1
Oi=umm+t=O -1
p=UH+t=O -6
t=I-LOC+w=Qasr 2
Oi=qasr+t=I-LOC 2
t=O+w=port 0
t=I-LOC+w=Gulf 3
Oi=gulf+t=I-LOC 5
t=I-LOC+w=Umm 3
Oi=umm+t=I-LOC 3
p=UH+t=I-LOC 0
t=I-LOC+w=DIGEST -1
Oi=digest+t=I-LOC -1
t=I-LOC+w=Lebanon 4
Oi=lebanon+t=I-LOC 4
t=I-LOC+w=Aug -1
Oi=aug+t=I-LOC -3
t=O+w=BEIRUT -5
Oi=beirut+t=O -6
t=I-LOC+w=BEIRUT 5
Oi=beirut+t=I-LOC 9
p=IN+t=I-LOC -1
t=O+w=Beirut -1
t=I-LOC+w=Beirut 4
t=I-LOC+w=AN-NAHAR -3
Oi=an-nahar+t=I-LOC -3
t=I-ORG+w=AN-NAHAR 5
Oi=an-nahar+t=I-ORG 5
t=O+w=Confrontation 0
Oi=confrontation+t=O 0
t=O+w=escalating 0
Oi=escalating+t=O 0
t=O+w=Hizbollah -2
Oi=hizbollah+t=O -2
t=I-ORG+w=Hizbollah 4
Oi=hizbollah+t=I-ORG 4
t=I-ORG+w=Hariri -1
Oi=hariri+t=I-ORG -1
t=O+w=threats 0
Oi=threats+t=O 0
t=O+w=serve 0
Oi=serve+t=O 0
t=I-PER+w=Hariri 4
Oi=hariri+t=I-PER 4
t=I-PER+w=AS-SAFIR -1
Oi=as-safir+t=I-PER -1
t=I-ORG+w=AS-SAFIR 5
Oi=as-safir+t=I-ORG 5
t=I-PER+w=Parliament -2
Oi=parliament+t=I-PER -2
t=I-PER+w=Speaker -5
Oi=speaker+t=I-PER -5
t=I-PER+w=Berri 3
Oi=berri+t=I-PER 3
t=O+w=preparing 0
Oi=preparing+t=O 0
t=I-ORG+w=Lebanon 2
Oi=lebanon+t=I-ORG 2
t=O+w=Parliament 5
t=O+w=Speaker 8
Oi=speaker+t=O 9
t=O+w=Parliamentary 4
Oi=parliamentary+t=O 5
t=O+w=battle 2
Oi=battle+t=O 1
t=O+w=.. 0
Oi=..+t=O 0
t=O+w=lists 0
Oi=lists+t=O 0
t=O+w=prepared 0
Oi=prepared+t=O 0
t=I-ORG+w=AL-ANWAR 5
Oi=al-anwar+t=I-ORG 5
t=O+w=Continued 0
Oi=continued+t=O 0
t=O+w=criticism 0
Oi=criticism+t=O 0
t=O+w=law -1
t=O+w=violation 0
Oi=violation+t=O 0
t=O+w=incidents 0
Oi=incidents+t=O 0
t=O+w=occurred 0
Oi=occurred+t=O 0
t=I-LOC+w=Mount 2
Oi=mount+t=I-LOC 2
t=I-ORG+w=AD-DIYAR 6
Oi=ad-diyar+t=I-ORG 6
t=O+w=Financial 3
Oi=financial+t=O 6
t=O+w=Lebanon -2
Oi=lebanon+t=O -2
t=O+w=Pakistan -3
Oi=pakistan+t=O -4
t=I-LOC+w=Pakistan 7
Oi=pakistan+t=I-LOC 13
t=I-LOC+w=Hariri -2
Oi=hariri+t=I-LOC -2
t=O+w=step 0
Oi=step+t=O 4
t=O+w=election 2
Oi=election+t=O 1
t=O+w=incomplete 2
Oi=incomplete+t=O 2
t=O+w=list 1
Oi=list+t=O 1
t=I-LOC+w=NIDA'A -1
Oi=nida'a+t=I-LOC -1
t=O+w=AL-WATAN -1
Oi=al-watan+t=O -1
t=I-ORG+w=NIDA'A 2
Oi=nida'a+t=I-ORG 2
t=I-ORG+w=AL-WATAN 2
Oi=al-watan+t=I-ORG 2
t=I-LOC+w=Maronite -2
Oi=maronite+t=I-LOC -2
t=O+w=Patriarch 6
Oi=patriarch+t=O 6
t=I-LOC+w=Sfeir -1
Oi=sfeir+t=I-LOC -1
t=O+w=sorrow 0
Oi=sorrow+t=O 0
t=O+w=violations 0
Oi=violations+t=O 0
t=I-ORG+w=Maronite 3
Oi=maronite+t=I-ORG 3
t=I-PER+w=Sfeir 4
Oi=sfeir+t=I-PER 4
t=I-PER+w=CME -1
Oi=cme+t=I-PER -1
t=O+w=live 1
Oi=live+t=O 1
t=O+w=feeder 0
Oi=feeder+t=O 0
t=O+w=calls 1
Oi=calls+t=O 6
t=O+w=range 1
Oi=range+t=O 1
t=O+w=mixed 2
Oi=mixed+t=O 2
t=I-ORG+w=CME 5
Oi=cme+t=I-ORG 5
t=I-ORG+w=CHICAGO -1
Oi=chicago+t=I-ORG 3
t=I-LOC+w=CHICAGO 1
Oi=chicago+t=I-LOC 6
t=O+w=Early 0
t=O+w=futures 2
Oi=futures+t=O 2
t=O+w=ranged 0
Oi=ranged+t=O 0
t=O+w=0.200 0
Oi=0.200+t=O 0
t=O+w=cent 0
Oi=cent+t=O 0
t=O+w=higher 1
Oi=higher+t=O 2
t=O+w=0.100 0
Oi=0.100+t=O 0
t=O+w=lower 3
Oi=lower+t=O 3
t=O+w=livestock 0
Oi=livestock+t=O 0
t=O+w=analysts 3
Oi=analysts+t=O 4
t=O+w=continued 0
t=O+w=strong 2
Oi=strong+t=O 7
t=O+w=tone 0
Oi=tone+t=O 0
t=O+w=cash 1
Oi=cash+t=O 1
t=O+w=markets 1
Oi=markets+t=O 3
t=O+w=prompt 1
Oi=prompt+t=O 1
t=I-ORG+w=Outlook -1
Oi=outlook+t=I-ORG -1
t=O+w=bullish 1
Oi=bullish+t=O 1
t=O+w=cattle-on-feed 0
Oi=cattle-on-feed+t=O 0
t=O+w=lend 0
Oi=lend+t=O 0
t=O+w=bull 0
Oi=bull+t=O 0
t=O+w=spreading 0
Oi=spreading+t=O 0
t=O+w=Outlook 1
Oi=outlook+t=O 2
t=O+w=However 1
Oi=however+t=O 2
t=O+w=likely 2
Oi=likely+t=O 2
t=O+w=prices 2
Oi=prices+t=O -3
t=O+w=drift 0
Oi=drift+t=O 0
t=O+w=evening 0
Oi=evening+t=O 0
t=O+w=ahead 1
Oi=ahead+t=O 1
t=O+w=Cash 0
t=O+w=record 1
Oi=record+t=O 7
t=O+w=amount 0
Oi=amount+t=O 7
t=O+w=feedlot 0
Oi=feedlot+t=O 0
t=O+w=traded 0
Oi=traded+t=O 0
t=I-LOC+w=Kindercare -1
Oi=kindercare+t=I-LOC -2
t=O+w=debt 0
Oi=debt+t=O 0
t=O+w=hit 1
Oi=hit+t=O 1
t=O+w=Q1 3
Oi=q1+t=O 3
t=O+w=results 0
Oi=results+t=O 9
t=O+w=Kindercare 3
Oi=kindercare+t=O 3
t=I-PER+w=MONTGOMERY -1
Oi=montgomery+t=I-PER -1
t=O+w=Ala -3
Oi=ala+t=O -3
t=I-LOC+w=MONTGOMERY 1
Oi=montgomery+t=I-LOC 1
t=I-LOC+w=Ala 3
Oi=ala+t=I-LOC 3
t=I-LOC+w=KinderCare -1
t=I-LOC+w=Learning -1
Oi=learning+t=I-LOC -1
t=O+w=Centers -1
Oi=centers+t=O 0
t=I-LOC+w=Inc -3
Oi=inc+t=I-LOC -3
t=O+w=buyback 0
Oi=buyback+t=O 0
t=O+w=mean 0
Oi=mean+t=O 0
t=O+w=extraordinary 1
Oi=extraordinary+t=O 1
t=O+w=loss 1
Oi=loss+t=O 1
t=O+w=1.2 0
Oi=1.2+t=O 0
t=O+w=fiscal 1
Oi=fiscal+t=O 3
t=O+w=1997 0
Oi=1997+t=O 0
t=O+w=first 5
t=I-ORG+w=KinderCare 1
Oi=kindercare+t=I-ORG 0
t=I-ORG+w=Learning 1
Oi=learning+t=I-ORG 1
t=I-ORG+w=Centers 1
Oi=centers+t=I-ORG 0
t=I-ORG+w=Inc 12
Oi=inc+t=I-ORG 12
t=O+w=company 2
Oi=company+t=O 5
t=O+w=began 1
Oi=began+t=O 1
t=I-ORG+w=June -1
Oi=june+t=I-ORG -1
t=O+w=1 1
Oi=1+t=O 1
t=O+w=30 1
Oi=30+t=O 1
t=O+w=par 4
Oi=par+t=O 4
t=O+w=value 0
Oi=value+t=O 4
t=O+w=outstanding 2
Oi=outstanding+t=O 2
t=O+w=10-3/8 0
Oi=10-3/8+t=O 0
t=O+w=notes 2
t=O+w=31.5 0
Oi=31.5+t=O 0
t=I-ORG+w=Philip 2
Oi=philip+t=I-ORG 2
t=I-PER+w=Maslowe 3
Oi=maslowe+t=I-PER 3
t=O+w=financial 3
t=O+w=officer 1
Oi=officer+t=O 1
t=O+w=preschool 0
Oi=preschool+t=O 0
t=O+w=child 0
Oi=child+t=O 7
t=O+w=care 1
Oi=care+t=O 0
t=O+w=offered 0
Oi=offered+t=O 4
t=O+w=opportunity 1
Oi=opportunity+t=O 1
t=O+w=reduce 0
Oi=reduce+t=O 0
t=O+w=weighted 0
Oi=weighted+t=O 0
t=O+w=average 2
Oi=average+t=O 2
t=O+w=interest 0
Oi=interest+t=O 3
t=O+w=costs 1
Oi=costs+t=O 1
t=O+w=improve 0
Oi=improve+t=O 0
t=O+w=future 1
Oi=future+t=O 6
t=O+w=flows 0
Oi=flows+t=O 0
t=O+w=earnings 1
Oi=earnings+t=O 1
t=I-PER+w=Philip 0
Oi=philip+t=I-PER 0
t=I-ORG+w=RESEARCH -4
Oi=research+t=I-ORG 2
t=I-PER+w=ALERT -1
Oi=alert+t=I-PER -1
t=I-PER+w=Lehman 0
Oi=lehman+t=I-PER 0
t=O+w=starts 5
Oi=starts+t=O 5
t=O+w=SNET -2
Oi=snet+t=O -2
t=O+w=RESEARCH 7
Oi=research+t=O 2
t=O+w=ALERT 6
Oi=alert+t=O 3
t=I-ORG+w=SNET 4
Oi=snet+t=I-ORG 4
t=O+w=analyst 4
Oi=analyst+t=O 4
t=O+w=Blake -1
Oi=blake+t=O -1
t=I-ORG+w=Bath -2
Oi=bath+t=I-ORG -2
t=O+w=started 2
Oi=started+t=O 2
t=O+w=Southern -7
t=O+w=New 0
t=I-ORG+w=England 2
Oi=england+t=I-ORG 0
t=O+w=Telecommunciations -2
Oi=telecommunciations+t=O -2
t=I-ORG+w=Corp 11
Oi=corp+t=I-ORG 11
t=O+w=outperform 0
Oi=outperform+t=O 0
t=O+w=rating 0
Oi=rating+t=O 3
t=I-PER+w=Blake 3
Oi=blake+t=I-PER 3
t=I-PER+w=Bath 3
Oi=bath+t=I-PER 3
t=I-ORG+w=Southern 8
Oi=southern+t=I-ORG 4
t=I-ORG+w=New 1
Oi=new+t=I-ORG 0
t=I-ORG+w=Telecommunciations 2
Oi=telecommunciations+t=I-ORG 2
t=O+w=12-month 0
Oi=12-month+t=O 0
t=O+w=price 2
t=O+w=target 2
Oi=target+t=O 2
t=O+w=45 0
Oi=45+t=O 0
t=O+w=estimate 0
Oi=estimate+t=O 0
t=O+w=3.09 0
Oi=3.09+t=O 0
t=O+w=per 5
Oi=per+t=O 1
t=O+w=share 1
Oi=share+t=O 1
t=O+w=immediately 1
Oi=immediately+t=O 1
t=O+w=available 1
Oi=available+t=O 2
t=B-MISC+w=New -1
ti=B-MISC+ti-1=I-ORG -1
Oi=new+t=B-MISC -1
ti=I-ORG+ti-1=B-MISC -8
t=O+w=closed 1
Oi=closed+t=O 1
t=O+w=38-1/2 0
Oi=38-1/2+t=O 0
t=I-PER+w=E. 2
Oi=e.+t=I-PER 2
t=I-ORG+w=Auchard -3
Oi=auchard+t=I-ORG -3
t=I-PER+w=Wall 3
Oi=wall+t=I-PER 1
t=I-ORG+w=Street 2
Oi=street+t=I-ORG 1
t=O+w=212-859-1736 0
Oi=212-859-1736+t=O 0
t=I-PER+w=Auchard 3
Oi=auchard+t=I-PER 3
t=I-ORG+w=Wall -3
Oi=wall+t=I-ORG 2
t=I-ORG+w=bureau 0
Oi=bureau+t=I-ORG 3
t=I-ORG+w=Gateway 0
Oi=gateway+t=I-ORG 0
t=I-MISC+w=Data -2
ti=I-MISC+ti-1=I-ORG -3
Oi=data+t=I-MISC -2
t=I-MISC+w=Sciences -1
Oi=sciences+t=I-MISC -1
t=I-ORG+w=Q2 -5
Oi=q2+t=I-ORG -5
t=O+w=net 3
Oi=net+t=O 3
t=O+w=rises 3
Oi=rises+t=O 3
t=I-ORG+w=Data 4
Oi=data+t=I-ORG 2
t=I-ORG+w=Sciences 3
Oi=sciences+t=I-ORG 3
t=O+w=Q2 5
Oi=q2+t=O 5
t=I-ORG+w=PHOENIX -2
Oi=phoenix+t=I-ORG -2
t=I-LOC+w=PHOENIX 3
Oi=phoenix+t=I-LOC 3
t=I-LOC+w=Summary -1
Oi=summary+t=I-LOC -1
t=I-PER+w=Consolidated -1
Oi=consolidated+t=I-PER -1
t=I-PER+w=Financial -3
Oi=financial+t=I-PER -4
t=I-PER+w=Data -1
Oi=data+t=I-PER -1
t=O+w=Summary 3
Oi=summary+t=O 7
t=I-ORG+w=Consolidated 1
Oi=consolidated+t=I-ORG 1
t=I-ORG+w=Financial -1
Oi=financial+t=I-ORG 1
t=O+w=In 1
t=O+w=Thousands 1
Oi=thousands+t=O 3
t=O+w=except 0
Oi=except+t=O 0
t=O+w=data 2
Oi=data+t=O 4
t=O+w=Six 0
t=O+w=Months 0
t=O+w=Ended 0
Oi=ended+t=O 2
t=I-ORG+w=Quarter -2
Oi=quarter+t=I-ORG -3
t=O+w=Quarter 2
t=O+w=Jul 4
Oi=jul+t=O 4
t=O+w=31 -2
Oi=31+t=O -2
t=I-ORG+w=Income -3
Oi=income+t=I-ORG -3
t=I-ORG+w=Statement -4
Oi=statement+t=I-ORG -5
t=O+w=Income 5
Oi=income+t=O 5
t=O+w=Statement 4
t=O+w=Data 2
t=O+w=Total -1
t=O+w=Revenue 2
Oi=revenue+t=O 7
t=O+w=10,756 0
Oi=10,756+t=O 0
t=O+w=13,102 0
Oi=13,102+t=O 0
t=O+w=7,961 0
Oi=7,961+t=O 0
t=O+w=5,507 0
Oi=5,507+t=O 0
t=O+w=Software 1
Oi=software+t=O 2
t=O+w=2,383 0
Oi=2,383+t=O 0
t=O+w=1,558 0
Oi=1,558+t=O 0
t=O+w=1,086 0
Oi=1,086+t=O 0
t=O+w=1,074 0
Oi=1,074+t=O 0
t=O+w=Services 2
Oi=services+t=O 4
t=O+w=1,154 0
Oi=1,154+t=O 0
t=O+w=692 0
Oi=692+t=O 0
t=O+w=624 0
Oi=624+t=O 0
t=O+w=465 0
Oi=465+t=O 0
t=O+w=Operating 0
Oi=operating+t=O 1
t=O+w=906 0
Oi=906+t=O 0
t=O+w=962 0
Oi=962+t=O 0
t=O+w=599 0
Oi=599+t=O 0
t=O+w=515 0
Oi=515+t=O 0
t=O+w=Net -3
t=O+w=821 0
Oi=821+t=O 0
t=O+w=512 0
Oi=512+t=O 0
t=O+w=565 0
Oi=565+t=O 0
t=O+w=301 0
Oi=301+t=O 0
t=O+w=Earnings 0
t=O+w=Per -4
t=O+w=Share 0
t=O+w=0.31 0
Oi=0.31+t=O 0
t=O+w=0.34 0
Oi=0.34+t=O 0
t=O+w=0.19 0
Oi=0.19+t=O 0
t=O+w=0.20 0
Oi=0.20+t=O 0
t=O+w=Jan 3
Oi=jan+t=O 3
t=O+w=Balance 3
Oi=balance+t=O 3
t=O+w=Sheet 5
t=O+w=Working 3
t=O+w=Capital 1
t=O+w=5,755 0
Oi=5,755+t=O 0
t=O+w=881 0
Oi=881+t=O 0
t=O+w=Equivalents 0
Oi=equivalents+t=O 0
t=O+w=2,386 0
Oi=2,386+t=O 0
t=O+w=93 0
Oi=93+t=O 0
t=O+w=Assets 0
Oi=assets+t=O 1
t=O+w=14,196 0
Oi=14,196+t=O 0
t=O+w=7,138 0
Oi=7,138+t=O 0
t=O+w=Shareholders 0
Oi=shareholders+t=O 1
t=O+w=Equity 0
Oi=equity+t=O 3
t=O+w=5,951 0
Oi=5,951+t=O 0
t=O+w=1,461 0
Oi=1,461+t=O 0
t=O+w=socialists 0
t=O+w=give 1
t=O+w=backing 1
Oi=backing+t=O 1
t=O+w=chooses 0
Oi=chooses+t=O 0
t=I-PER+w=Thursday -1
Oi=thursday+t=I-PER -1
t=I-PER+w=+301 -1
Oi=+301+t=I-PER -1
t=O+w=Le -2
Oi=le+t=O -4
t=O+w=Monde -3
Oi=monde+t=O -3
t=I-ORG+w=Le 4
Oi=le+t=I-ORG 8
t=I-ORG+w=Monde 2
Oi=monde+t=I-ORG 3
t=I-ORG+w=PARIS -4
Oi=paris+t=I-ORG 0
t=I-LOC+w=PARIS 6
Oi=paris+t=I-LOC 7
t=I-MISC+w=leading -1
Oi=leading+t=I-MISC -1
t=O+w=afternoon 1
Oi=afternoon+t=O 1
t=I-MISC+w=daily -1
Oi=daily+t=I-MISC -4
t=O+w=dated 0
Oi=dated+t=O 0
t=O+w=23 1
Oi=23+t=O 1
t=O+w=daily 7
t=I-LOC+w=FRONT -1
Oi=front+t=I-LOC -4
t=I-ORG+w=PAGE -3
Oi=page+t=I-ORG -3
t=O+w=FRONT 7
Oi=front+t=O 5
t=O+w=PAGE 5
Oi=page+t=O 5
t=O+w=Africans -2
Oi=africans+t=O -2
t=O+w=seeking 0
Oi=seeking+t=O 0
t=O+w=renew 0
Oi=renew+t=O 0
t=O+w=obtain 0
Oi=obtain+t=O 0
t=O+w=residence 1
Oi=residence+t=O 1
t=O+w=rights 3
Oi=rights+t=O 3
t=O+w=say 2
Oi=say+t=O 6
t=O+w=Alain -1
Oi=alain+t=O -1
t=O+w=Juppe -3
Oi=juppe+t=O -3
t=O+w=proposals 0
Oi=proposals+t=O 0
t=O+w=insufficient 0
Oi=insufficient+t=O 0
t=O+w=hunger 0
Oi=hunger+t=O -1
t=O+w=strike 2
Oi=strike+t=O 6
t=O+w=enters 0
Oi=enters+t=O 0
t=O+w=49th 0
Oi=49th+t=O 0
t=O+w=day 4
Oi=day+t=O 4
t=O+w=Paris -4
Oi=paris+t=O -4
t=O+w=church 1
Oi=church+t=O 5
t=O+w=rally 2
Oi=rally+t=O -2
t=O+w=attracts 0
Oi=attracts+t=O 0
t=O+w=8,000 0
Oi=8,000+t=O 0
t=O+w=sympathisers 0
Oi=sympathisers+t=O 0
t=I-MISC+w=Africans 5
Oi=africans+t=I-MISC 5
t=I-PER+w=Alain 2
Oi=alain+t=I-PER 2
t=I-PER+w=Juppe 7
Oi=juppe+t=I-PER 7
t=I-LOC+w=Paris 1
t=I-PER+w=FLNC -1
Oi=flnc+t=I-PER -1
t=I-PER+w=Corsican -1
Oi=corsican+t=I-PER -1
t=O+w=nationalist 2
Oi=nationalist+t=O 1
t=O+w=announces 0
Oi=announces+t=O 0
t=O+w=truce 1
Oi=truce+t=O 1
t=O+w=night 2
Oi=night+t=O 2
t=I-ORG+w=FLNC 6
Oi=flnc+t=I-ORG 6
t=I-MISC+w=Corsican 9
Oi=corsican+t=I-MISC 9
t=I-LOC+w=BUSINESS -1
Oi=business+t=I-LOC -1
t=I-ORG+w=PAGES -3
Oi=pages+t=I-ORG -3
t=O+w=BUSINESS 1
Oi=business+t=O 3
t=O+w=PAGES 4
Oi=pages+t=O 4
t=O+w=Shutdown 0
Oi=shutdown+t=O 1
t=I-LOC+w=Bally -1
Oi=bally+t=I-LOC -1
t=O+w=French -5
Oi=french+t=O -4
t=O+w=factories 0
Oi=factories+t=O 0
t=O+w=points 3
Oi=points+t=O 3
t=O+w=shoe 0
Oi=shoe+t=O 0
t=O+w=industry 2
Oi=industry+t=O 3
t=O+w=undercut 0
Oi=undercut+t=O 0
t=O+w=low-wage 0
Oi=low-wage+t=O 0
t=O+w=competition 1
Oi=competition+t=O 5
t=O+w=failure 1
Oi=failure+t=O 1
t=O+w=keep 1
Oi=keep+t=O 1
t=O+w=abreast 0
Oi=abreast+t=O 0
t=O+w=trends 0
Oi=trends+t=O 4
t=I-ORG+w=Bally 4
Oi=bally+t=I-ORG 4
t=I-MISC+w=French 6
Oi=french+t=I-MISC 9
t=I-ORG+w=Secretary -4
Oi=secretary+t=I-ORG -4
t=I-MISC+w=general -2
Oi=general+t=I-MISC 1
t=I-MISC+w=Sud-PTT 5
Oi=sud-ptt+t=I-MISC 5
t=I-MISC+w=union -1
Oi=union+t=I-MISC -5
t=I-ORG+w=France 0
Oi=france+t=I-ORG 0
t=I-MISC+w=Telecom -1
Oi=telecom+t=I-MISC -1
p=PDT+t=O 3
t=I-MISC+w=elements -1
Oi=elements+t=I-MISC -1
t=I-MISC+w=place -1
Oi=place+t=I-MISC -1
t=I-MISC+w=social -1
Oi=social+t=I-MISC 0
t=O+w=unrest 0
Oi=unrest+t=O 0
t=I-MISC+w=next -1
Oi=next+t=I-MISC -1
t=I-MISC+w=weeks -1
Oi=weeks+t=I-MISC -1
t=O+w=Secretary 10
t=O+w=union 6
Oi=union+t=O -2
t=I-ORG+w=Telecom 5
Oi=telecom+t=I-ORG 8
t=O+w=elements 1
Oi=elements+t=O 1
t=O+w=social 1
Oi=social+t=O 2
t=O+w=weeks 1
Oi=weeks+t=O 1
t=O+w=+33 0
Oi=+33+t=O 0
t=O+w=42 0
Oi=42+t=O 0
t=O+w=21 0
Oi=21+t=O 0
t=O+w=53 0
Oi=53+t=O 0
t=O+w=81 0
Oi=81+t=O 0
t=I-ORG+w=Paris 4
t=O+w=Well 0
Oi=well+t=O 1
t=O+w=repairs 0
Oi=repairs+t=O 0
t=O+w=lift 1
Oi=lift+t=O 1
t=O+w=Heidrun -4
Oi=heidrun+t=O -4
t=O+w=oil 1
Oi=oil+t=O 0
t=O+w=output 1
Oi=output+t=O 1
t=O+w=Statoil -3
Oi=statoil+t=O -3
t=I-LOC+w=Heidrun 7
Oi=heidrun+t=I-LOC 7
t=I-ORG+w=Statoil 4
Oi=statoil+t=I-ORG 4
t=I-ORG+w=OSLO -2
Oi=oslo+t=I-ORG -2
t=I-LOC+w=OSLO 3
Oi=oslo+t=I-LOC 8
t=O+w=plugged 0
Oi=plugged+t=O 0
t=O+w=water 1
Oi=water+t=O 3
t=O+w=injection 0
Oi=injection+t=O 0
t=O+w=wells 1
Oi=wells+t=O 0
t=O+w=oilfield 0
Oi=oilfield+t=O 0
t=O+w=off 2
t=O+w=mid-Norway -4
Oi=mid-norway+t=O -4
t=O+w=reopened 1
Oi=reopened+t=O 1
t=O+w=operator 2
Oi=operator+t=O 2
t=I-ORG+w=Den 1
Oi=den+t=I-ORG 0
t=I-ORG+w=Norske 1
Oi=norske+t=I-ORG 1
t=I-ORG+w=Stats 1
Oi=stats+t=I-ORG 1
t=I-ORG+w=Oljeselskap 1
Oi=oljeselskap+t=I-ORG 1
t=I-ORG+w=AS 0
Oi=as+t=I-ORG 0
t=I-MISC+w=mid-Norway 4
Oi=mid-norway+t=I-MISC 4
t=O+w=accounted 1
Oi=accounted+t=O 1
t=O+w=dip 0
Oi=dip+t=O 0
t=O+w=30,000 0
Oi=30,000+t=O 0
t=O+w=barrels 1
Oi=barrels+t=O 1
t=O+w=bpd 2
Oi=bpd+t=O 2
t=O+w=roughly 1
Oi=roughly+t=O 1
t=O+w=220,000 0
Oi=220,000+t=O 0
t=O+w=according 1
Oi=according+t=O 2
t=I-ORG+w=Status 1
Oi=status+t=I-ORG 1
t=I-ORG+w=Weekly 1
Oi=weekly+t=I-ORG -1
t=O+w=newsletter 2
Oi=newsletter+t=O 2
t=O+w=reperforated 0
Oi=reperforated+t=O 0
t=O+w=gravel 0
Oi=gravel+t=O 0
t=O+w=pumped 0
Oi=pumped+t=O 0
t=O+w=reservoir 0
Oi=reservoir+t=O 0
t=O+w=plugging 0
Oi=plugging+t=O 0
t=O+w=problems 2
Oi=problems+t=O 2
t=O+w=Oslo -5
Oi=oslo+t=O -5
t=I-ORG+w=newsroom -6
t=O+w=+47 0
Oi=+47+t=O 0
t=O+w=50 1
Oi=50+t=O 1
t=O+w=41 0
Oi=41+t=O 0
t=I-LOC+w=Oslo 5
t=O+w=newsroom 6
t=O+w=Finnish -3
Oi=finnish+t=O -5
t=I-LOC+w=April -3
Oi=april+t=I-LOC -3
t=O+w=surplus 1
Oi=surplus+t=O 1
t=O+w=3.8 0
Oi=3.8+t=O 0
t=O+w=billion 1
Oi=billion+t=O 1
t=O+w=markka 1
Oi=markka+t=O 1
t=I-LOC+w=NCB -1
Oi=ncb+t=I-LOC -1
t=I-MISC+w=Finnish 3
Oi=finnish+t=I-MISC 6
t=O+w=April 7
Oi=april+t=O 7
t=I-ORG+w=NCB 3
Oi=ncb+t=I-ORG 3
t=I-ORG+w=HELSINKI -1
Oi=helsinki+t=I-ORG -1
t=I-LOC+w=HELSINKI 4
Oi=helsinki+t=I-LOC 7
t=O+w=Finland -5
Oi=finland+t=O -5
t=O+w=3.83 0
Oi=3.83+t=O 0
t=I-ORG+w=April -2
Oi=april+t=I-ORG -2
t=O+w=3.43 0
Oi=3.43+t=O 0
t=I-ORG+w=Customs 0
Oi=customs+t=I-ORG -1
t=I-ORG+w=Board 6
Oi=board+t=I-ORG 4
t=I-LOC+w=Finland 4
Oi=finland+t=I-LOC 6
t=O+w=exports 2
Oi=exports+t=O 2
t=O+w=year-on-year 0
Oi=year-on-year+t=O 0
t=O+w=NCB -2
Oi=ncb+t=O -2
t=O+w=Trade 2
t=O+w=balance 0
t=O+w=96 -3
Oi=96+t=O -3
t=O+w=Jan-April 1
Oi=jan-april+t=O 1
p=''+t=O -1
t=O+w=95 -2
Oi=95+t=O -2
t=O+w=Imports 0
t=O+w=10,663 0
Oi=10,663+t=O 0
t=O+w=10,725 0
Oi=10,725+t=O 0
t=O+w=43,430 0
Oi=43,430+t=O 0
t=O+w=40,989 0
Oi=40,989+t=O 0
t=O+w=Exports 0
t=O+w=14,494 0
Oi=14,494+t=O 0
t=O+w=14,153 0
Oi=14,153+t=O 0
t=O+w=56,126 0
Oi=56,126+t=O 0
t=O+w=56,261 0
Oi=56,261+t=O 0
t=I-LOC+w=Balance -1
Oi=balance+t=I-LOC -1
t=O+w=+3,831 0
Oi=+3,831+t=O 0
t=O+w=+3,428 0
Oi=+3,428+t=O 0
t=O+w=+12,696 0
Oi=+12,696+t=O 0
t=O+w=+15,272 0
Oi=+15,272+t=O 0
t=O+w=January-April 2
Oi=january-april+t=O 2
t=O+w=import 2
Oi=import+t=O -1
t=O+w=revised 0
Oi=revised+t=O 0
t=O+w=39,584 0
Oi=39,584+t=O 0
t=O+w=export 1
Oi=export+t=O 3
t=O+w=55,627 0
Oi=55,627+t=O 0
t=O+w=Bank -1
Oi=bank+t=O 3
t=O+w=3.2 0
Oi=3.2+t=O 0
t=O+w=projected 0
Oi=projected+t=O 0
t=O+w=14.5 0
Oi=14.5+t=O 0
t=O+w=11.3 0
Oi=11.3+t=O 0
t=I-ORG+w=Bank 7
Oi=bank+t=I-ORG 5
t=I-ORG+w=Finland 3
Oi=finland+t=I-ORG 2
t=O+w=monthly 0
Oi=monthly+t=O 6
t=O+w=statistics 2
Oi=statistics+t=O 0
t=O+w=lagging 0
Oi=lagging+t=O 0
t=O+w=behind 1
Oi=behind+t=O 1
t=O+w=customs 1
Oi=customs+t=O 1
t=O+w=procedures 0
Oi=procedures+t=O 0
t=O+w=when 2
t=O+w=joined 0
Oi=joined+t=O 0
t=O+w=start 1
Oi=start+t=O 1
t=I-ORG+w=Helsinki 0
t=O+w=+358 0
Oi=+358+t=O 0
t=O+w=0 3
Oi=0+t=O 3
t=O+w=680 0
Oi=680+t=O 0
t=O+w=245 0
Oi=245+t=O 0
t=O+w=Dutch -6
Oi=dutch+t=O -8
t=O+w=raises 0
Oi=raises+t=O 0
t=O+w=tap 0
Oi=tap+t=O 0
t=O+w=sale 2
t=O+w=99.95 0
Oi=99.95+t=O 0
t=I-MISC+w=Dutch 5
Oi=dutch+t=I-MISC 10
t=O+w=AMSTERDAM -2
Oi=amsterdam+t=O -9
t=I-LOC+w=AMSTERDAM 7
Oi=amsterdam+t=I-LOC 12
t=I-ORG+w=Finance 3
Oi=finance+t=I-ORG 3
t=O+w=raised 0
Oi=raised+t=O 0
t=I-LOC+w=for -2
Oi=for+t=I-LOC -3
t=O+w=sales 2
Oi=sales+t=O 2
t=I-LOC+w=of 0
Oi=of+t=I-LOC 4
t=I-LOC+w=Dutch -1
Oi=dutch+t=I-LOC -1
t=I-LOC+w=new -2
Oi=new+t=I-LOC 3
t=O+w=5.75 0
Oi=5.75+t=O 0
t=I-LOC+w=percent -1
Oi=percent+t=I-LOC -1
t=I-ORG+w=due -1
Oi=due+t=I-ORG -1
t=I-ORG+w=September -3
Oi=september+t=I-ORG -3
t=O+w=2002 0
Oi=2002+t=O 0
t=O+w=99.90 0
Oi=99.90+t=O 0
t=O+w=September 8
Oi=september+t=O 8
t=O+w=Tap 0
t=O+w=being 2
Oi=being+t=O 2
t=O+w=07.00 0
Oi=07.00+t=O 0
t=O+w=GMT -9
Oi=gmt+t=O -6
t=O+w=15.00 0
Oi=15.00+t=O 0
t=O+w=notice 2
Oi=notice+t=O 2
t=I-MISC+w=GMT 11
Oi=gmt+t=I-MISC 8
t=O+w=2.3 0
Oi=2.3+t=O 0
t=O+w=guilders 0
Oi=guilders+t=O 0
t=O+w=close 3
Oi=close+t=O 9
t=O+w=Amsterdam -7
t=O+w=+31 0
Oi=+31+t=O 0
t=O+w=20 0
Oi=20+t=O 0
t=O+w=504 0
Oi=504+t=O 0
t=O+w=5000 0
Oi=5000+t=O 0
t=I-LOC+w=Amsterdam 5
t=O+w=tells 0
Oi=tells+t=O 0
t=O+w=BONN -6
Oi=bonn+t=O -6
t=I-LOC+w=BONN 7
t=I-ORG+w=Agriculture 3
Oi=agriculture+t=I-ORG 3
t=O+w=meat 0
Oi=meat+t=O 0
t=O+w=animals 0
Oi=animals+t=O 0
t=O+w=Until 0
t=O+w=cleared 0
Oi=cleared+t=O 0
t=O+w=panels 0
Oi=panels+t=O 0
t=O+w=done 0
Oi=done+t=O 0
t=O+w=quickly 0
Oi=quickly+t=O 0
t=O+w=preference 0
Oi=preference+t=O 0
t=I-MISC+w=Zwingmann -1
Oi=zwingmann+t=I-MISC -1
t=I-ORG+w=ZDF 5
Oi=zdf+t=I-ORG 5
t=O+w=I 2
Oi=i+t=O 1
t=O+w=concrete 0
Oi=concrete+t=O 0
t=O+w=too 0
Oi=too+t=O 0
t=O+w=many 3
Oi=many+t=O 3
t=O+w=holes 1
Oi=holes+t=O 1
t=O+w=know 0
Oi=know+t=O 0
t=O+w=filled 1
Oi=filled+t=O 1
t=O+w=ensure 1
Oi=ensure+t=O 1
t=O+w=protection 1
Oi=protection+t=O 1
t=O+w=tops 0
Oi=tops+t=O 0
t=O+w=priorities 0
Oi=priorities+t=O 0
t=O+w=dealing 0
Oi=dealing+t=O 0
t=O+w=erupted 0
Oi=erupted+t=O 0
t=I-PER+w=Britain -2
Oi=britain+t=I-PER -2
t=O+w=acknowledged 0
Oi=acknowledged+t=O 0
t=O+w=rethink 0
Oi=rethink+t=O 0
t=O+w=use 1
Oi=use+t=O 1
t=O+w=suspect 0
Oi=suspect+t=O 0
t=O+w=tissue 0
Oi=tissue+t=O 0
t=O+w=experts 0
Oi=experts+t=O 2
t=I-PER+w=Farm -1
Oi=farm+t=I-PER -1
t=I-PER+w=Commissioner -2
Oi=commissioner+t=I-PER -2
t=O+w=banning 1
Oi=banning+t=O 1
t=I-ORG+w=Bovine -3
Oi=bovine+t=I-ORG -3
t=I-ORG+w=Spongiform -3
Oi=spongiform+t=I-ORG -3
t=I-LOC+w=Encephalopathy -1
Oi=encephalopathy+t=I-LOC -1
t=O+w=members 3
Oi=members+t=O 5
t=O+w=given 3
Oi=given+t=O -2
t=O+w=question 1
Oi=question+t=O 1
t=O+w=studied 0
Oi=studied+t=O 0
t=O+w=separately 0
Oi=separately+t=O 0
t=I-MISC+w=Sheep -1
Oi=sheep+t=I-MISC -1
t=O+w=perfectly 0
Oi=perfectly+t=O 0
t=O+w=safe 0
Oi=safe+t=O 0
t=O+w=eat 0
Oi=eat+t=O 0
t=I-MISC+w=ZDF -1
Oi=zdf+t=I-MISC -1
t=O+w=Germany -3
Oi=germany+t=O -5
t=O+w=After 0
t=O+w=admitted 0
Oi=admitted+t=O 0
t=O+w=link 0
Oi=link+t=O 0
t=O+w=fatal 1
Oi=fatal+t=O 1
t=O+w=equivalent 1
Oi=equivalent+t=O 1
t=O+w=worldwide 2
Oi=worldwide+t=O 5
t=I-LOC+w=EU -1
Oi=eu+t=I-LOC -1
t=O+w=summit 1
Oi=summit+t=O 1
t=O+w=progressive 0
Oi=progressive+t=O 0
t=O+w=takes 1
Oi=takes+t=O 5
t=O+w=parallel 0
Oi=parallel+t=O 0
t=O+w=eradicate 0
Oi=eradicate+t=O 0
t=O+w=GOLF -5
Oi=golf+t=O 0
t=O+w=SCORES 7
Oi=scores+t=O 8
t=O+w=AT 13
t=O+w=WORLD -5
Oi=world+t=O 2
t=O+w=SERIES -2
Oi=series+t=O 3
t=O+w=OF 0
t=I-MISC+w=WORLD 5
Oi=world+t=I-MISC 6
t=I-MISC+w=SERIES 4
Oi=series+t=I-MISC 5
t=I-MISC+w=OF 1
Oi=of+t=I-MISC 2
t=I-MISC+w=GOLF 3
Oi=golf+t=I-MISC 5
t=I-LOC+w=AKRON 4
Oi=akron+t=I-LOC 4
t=I-MISC+w=Ohio -1
Oi=ohio+t=I-MISC -1
t=I-LOC+w=Ohio 8
Oi=ohio+t=I-LOC 8
t=I-LOC+w=Scores -1
Oi=scores+t=I-LOC -2
t=O+w=2.1 0
Oi=2.1+t=O 0
t=O+w=Scores 1
t=I-MISC+w=NEC 1
Oi=nec+t=I-MISC 1
t=I-MISC+w=World 5
t=I-MISC+w=Series 3
t=I-LOC+w=Golf -4
Oi=golf+t=I-LOC 1
t=I-MISC+w=first -2
Oi=first+t=I-MISC 1
t=I-MISC+w=round -2
Oi=round+t=I-MISC -3
t=I-MISC+w=of 1
t=I-MISC+w=Golf 5
t=O+w=round 3
Oi=round+t=O 8
t=O+w=7,149 1
Oi=7,149+t=O 1
t=O+w=yard 2
Oi=yard+t=O 2
t=O+w=70 1
Oi=70+t=O 1
t=I-MISC+w=Firestone -2
Oi=firestone+t=I-MISC -2
t=I-MISC+w=C.C -2
Oi=c.c+t=I-MISC -2
t=I-MISC+w=course -1
Oi=course+t=I-MISC -1
t=I-LOC+w=Firestone 5
Oi=firestone+t=I-LOC 5
t=I-LOC+w=C.C 5
Oi=c.c+t=I-LOC 5
t=O+w=course 1
Oi=course+t=O 4
t=O+w=players 1
Oi=players+t=O 6
t=O+w=unless 1
Oi=unless+t=O 1
t=O+w=stated 2
Oi=stated+t=O 2
t=O+w=66 0
Oi=66+t=O 0
t=I-ORG+w=Paul -1
Oi=paul+t=I-ORG -1
t=I-LOC+w=Goydos -1
Oi=goydos+t=I-LOC -1
t=I-ORG+w=Billy -1
Oi=billy+t=I-ORG -1
t=I-LOC+w=Mayfair -1
Oi=mayfair+t=I-LOC -1
t=I-ORG+w=Hidemichi -1
Oi=hidemichi+t=I-ORG -1
t=I-LOC+w=Tanaka -1
Oi=tanaka+t=I-LOC -1
t=I-LOC+w=Japan 4
Oi=japan+t=I-LOC 4
t=I-PER+w=Paul 7
Oi=paul+t=I-PER 7
t=I-PER+w=Goydos 3
Oi=goydos+t=I-PER 3
t=I-PER+w=Billy 3
Oi=billy+t=I-PER 3
t=I-PER+w=Mayfair 7
Oi=mayfair+t=I-PER 7
t=I-PER+w=Hidemichi 4
Oi=hidemichi+t=I-PER 4
t=I-PER+w=Tanaka 2
Oi=tanaka+t=I-PER 2
t=O+w=68 0
Oi=68+t=O 0
t=I-PER+w=Steve 5
Oi=steve+t=I-PER 5
t=I-PER+w=Stricker 1
Oi=stricker+t=I-PER 1
t=O+w=69 0
Oi=69+t=O 0
t=I-PER+w=Justin 2
Oi=justin+t=I-PER 2
t=I-PER+w=Leonard 2
Oi=leonard+t=I-PER 2
t=I-PER+w=Mark 7
Oi=mark+t=I-PER 5
t=I-PER+w=Brooks 3
Oi=brooks+t=I-PER 3
t=I-PER+w=Tim 3
Oi=tim+t=I-PER 3
t=I-PER+w=Herron 1
Oi=herron+t=I-PER 1
t=I-PER+w=Duffy 2
Oi=duffy+t=I-PER 2
t=I-PER+w=Waldorf 2
Oi=waldorf+t=I-PER 2
t=I-PER+w=Davis 3
Oi=davis+t=I-PER 3
t=I-PER+w=Love 4
Oi=love+t=I-PER 2
t=I-PER+w=Anders 2
Oi=anders+t=I-PER 2
t=O+w=Forsbrand -2
Oi=forsbrand+t=O -2
t=I-PER+w=Forsbrand 2
Oi=forsbrand+t=I-PER 2
t=I-PER+w=Sweden -2
Oi=sweden+t=I-PER -2
t=I-PER+w=Nick 3
Oi=nick+t=I-PER 3
t=I-PER+w=Faldo 0
Oi=faldo+t=I-PER 0
t=I-PER+w=Cook 0
Oi=cook+t=I-PER 0
t=I-PER+w=Phil 2
Oi=phil+t=I-PER 2
t=I-LOC+w=Sweden 6
t=O+w=Mickelson -4
Oi=mickelson+t=O -4
t=I-PER+w=Greg 4
Oi=greg+t=I-PER 4
t=I-PER+w=Norman 6
Oi=norman+t=I-PER 6
t=I-PER+w=Australia -3
Oi=australia+t=I-PER -5
t=I-PER+w=Mickelson 5
Oi=mickelson+t=I-PER 7
t=I-LOC+w=Australia 3
Oi=australia+t=I-LOC 8
t=O+w=71 0
Oi=71+t=O 0
t=I-PER+w=Ernie 2
Oi=ernie+t=I-PER 2
t=I-PER+w=Els 2
Oi=els+t=I-PER 2
t=I-PER+w=South -5
Oi=south+t=I-PER -8
t=I-PER+w=Africa -4
Oi=africa+t=I-PER -6
t=I-PER+w=Scott 3
Oi=scott+t=I-PER 3
t=I-PER+w=Hoch 0
Oi=hoch+t=I-PER 0
t=I-LOC+w=South 7
Oi=south+t=I-LOC 6
t=I-LOC+w=Africa 6
Oi=africa+t=I-LOC 8
t=O+w=72 0
Oi=72+t=O 0
t=I-LOC+w=Clarence -1
Oi=clarence+t=I-LOC -1
t=I-LOC+w=Rose -1
Oi=rose+t=I-LOC -1
t=I-LOC+w=Loren -1
Oi=loren+t=I-LOC -1
t=I-LOC+w=Roberts -1
Oi=roberts+t=I-LOC -1
t=I-LOC+w=Fred -1
Oi=fred+t=I-LOC -1
t=I-LOC+w=Funk -1
Oi=funk+t=I-LOC -1
t=I-LOC+w=Sven -1
Oi=sven+t=I-LOC -1
t=I-LOC+w=Struver -1
Oi=struver+t=I-LOC -1
t=I-PER+w=Clarence 2
Oi=clarence+t=I-PER 2
t=I-PER+w=Rose 4
Oi=rose+t=I-PER 4
t=I-PER+w=Loren 2
Oi=loren+t=I-PER 2
t=I-PER+w=Roberts 2
Oi=roberts+t=I-PER 2
t=I-PER+w=Fred 2
Oi=fred+t=I-PER 2
t=I-PER+w=Funk 1
Oi=funk+t=I-PER 1
t=I-PER+w=Sven 1
Oi=sven+t=I-PER 1
t=I-PER+w=Struver 1
Oi=struver+t=I-PER 1
t=I-PER+w=Alexander 6
Oi=alexander+t=I-PER 6
t=I-PER+w=Cejka 0
Oi=cejka+t=I-PER 0
t=I-PER+w=Hal 2
Oi=hal+t=I-PER 2
t=I-PER+w=Sutton 2
Oi=sutton+t=I-PER 2
t=I-PER+w=Tom 4
Oi=tom+t=I-PER 4
t=O+w=73 1
Oi=73+t=O 1
t=I-PER+w=D.A. 2
Oi=d.a.+t=I-PER 2
t=I-PER+w=Weibring 2
Oi=weibring+t=I-PER 2
t=I-PER+w=Brad 3
Oi=brad+t=I-PER 3
t=I-PER+w=Bryant 1
Oi=bryant+t=I-PER 1
t=I-PER+w=Craig 4
Oi=craig+t=I-PER 4
t=I-PER+w=Parry 0
Oi=parry+t=I-PER 0
t=I-PER+w=Stewart 3
Oi=stewart+t=I-PER 3
t=I-PER+w=Ginn 0
Oi=ginn+t=I-PER 0
t=I-PER+w=Corey 2
Oi=corey+t=I-PER 2
t=I-PER+w=Pavin 1
Oi=pavin+t=I-PER 1
t=I-PER+w=Stadler -1
Oi=stadler+t=I-PER -1
t=I-PER+w=O'Meara 2
Oi=o'meara+t=I-PER 2
t=I-PER+w=Couples 5
Oi=couples+t=I-PER 5
t=O+w=74 0
Oi=74+t=O 0
t=I-PER+w=Stankowski 0
Oi=stankowski+t=I-PER 0
t=I-PER+w=Costantino 2
Oi=costantino+t=I-PER 2
t=I-PER+w=Rocca 2
Oi=rocca+t=I-PER 2
t=I-PER+w=Italy -3
Oi=italy+t=I-PER -3
t=I-LOC+w=Italy 7
Oi=italy+t=I-LOC 7
t=O+w=75 0
Oi=75+t=O 0
t=I-PER+w=Jim 6
Oi=jim+t=I-PER 6
t=I-PER+w=Furyk 0
Oi=furyk+t=I-PER 0
t=I-PER+w=Satoshi 2
Oi=satoshi+t=I-PER 2
t=I-PER+w=Higashi 2
Oi=higashi+t=I-PER 2
t=I-PER+w=Willie 2
Oi=willie+t=I-PER 2
t=I-PER+w=Wood 1
Oi=wood+t=I-PER 1
t=I-PER+w=Shigeki 1
Oi=shigeki+t=I-PER 1
t=I-LOC+w=Maruyama -1
Oi=maruyama+t=I-LOC -1
t=I-PER+w=Maruyama 2
Oi=maruyama+t=I-PER 2
t=O+w=76 1
Oi=76+t=O 1
t=I-PER+w=McCarron 0
Oi=mccarron+t=I-PER 0
t=O+w=77 0
Oi=77+t=O 0
t=I-PER+w=Wayne 6
Oi=wayne+t=I-PER 6
t=I-PER+w=Westner 0
Oi=westner+t=I-PER 0
t=I-PER+w=Schneiter 0
Oi=schneiter+t=I-PER 0
t=O+w=79 0
Oi=79+t=O 0
t=I-PER+w=Watson 0
Oi=watson+t=I-PER 0
t=I-PER+w=Seiki 1
Oi=seiki+t=I-PER 1
t=I-PER+w=Okuda 1
Oi=okuda+t=I-PER 1
t=I-LOC+w=SOCCER -1
Oi=soccer+t=I-LOC -1
t=I-LOC+w=GLORIA -1
Oi=gloria+t=I-LOC -3
t=O+w=BISTRITA -1
Oi=bistrita+t=O -1
t=I-LOC+w=BEAT -1
Oi=beat+t=I-LOC -2
t=O+w=2-1 2
Oi=2-1+t=O 2
t=O+w=F.C. -3
Oi=f.c.+t=O -3
t=I-LOC+w=VALLETTA 2
Oi=valletta+t=I-LOC 5
t=O+w=SOCCER 5
Oi=soccer+t=O 4
t=I-ORG+w=GLORIA 4
Oi=gloria+t=I-ORG 6
t=I-ORG+w=BISTRITA 1
Oi=bistrita+t=I-ORG 2
t=O+w=BEAT 4
Oi=beat+t=O 8
t=I-ORG+w=F.C. 6
Oi=f.c.+t=I-ORG 6
t=I-ORG+w=VALLETTA 0
Oi=valletta+t=I-ORG 0
t=I-LOC+w=BISTRITA 2
Oi=bistrita+t=I-LOC 4
t=I-PER+w=Gloria 0
Oi=gloria+t=I-PER -2
t=I-PER+w=Bistrita -3
Oi=bistrita+t=I-PER -5
t=I-LOC+w=Romania 5
Oi=romania+t=I-LOC 8
t=O+w=beat 4
t=O+w=halftime 1
Oi=halftime+t=O 5
t=O+w=1-1 7
Oi=1-1+t=O 7
t=I-PER+w=F.C. -3
Oi=f.c.+t=I-PER -3
t=I-PER+w=Valletta -2
Oi=valletta+t=I-PER -3
t=I-LOC+w=Malta 6
Oi=malta+t=I-LOC 6
t=I-LOC+w=Cup -2
Oi=cup+t=I-LOC -2
t=O+w=winners 3
Oi=winners+t=O 2
t=O+w=match 2
Oi=match+t=O 8
t=O+w=leg 3
Oi=leg+t=O 3
t=O+w=preliminary 3
Oi=preliminary+t=O 3
t=I-ORG+w=Gloria 2
t=I-ORG+w=Bistrita 1
t=I-ORG+w=Valletta 0
t=I-MISC+w=Cup 7
Oi=cup+t=I-MISC 12
t=I-MISC+w=winners -3
Oi=winners+t=I-MISC 3
t=O+w=Scorers 3
Oi=scorers+t=O 3
t=I-ORG+w=Ilie -1
Oi=ilie+t=I-ORG -1
t=I-ORG+w=Lazar -1
Oi=lazar+t=I-ORG -1
t=O+w=32nd 1
Oi=32nd+t=O 1
t=I-ORG+w=Eugen -1
Oi=eugen+t=I-ORG -1
t=I-ORG+w=Voica -1
Oi=voica+t=I-ORG -1
t=O+w=84th 2
Oi=84th+t=O 2
t=I-PER+w=Ilie 2
Oi=ilie+t=I-PER 2
t=I-PER+w=Lazar 2
Oi=lazar+t=I-PER 2
t=I-PER+w=Eugen 2
Oi=eugen+t=I-PER 2
t=I-PER+w=Voica 2
Oi=voica+t=I-PER 2
t=I-PER+w=La -5
Oi=la+t=I-PER -4
t=I-MISC+w=Gilbert -1
Oi=gilbert+t=I-MISC -1
t=I-MISC+w=Agius -1
Oi=agius+t=I-MISC -1
t=O+w=24th 2
Oi=24th+t=O 2
t=I-ORG+w=La 5
Oi=la+t=I-ORG 5
t=I-PER+w=Gilbert 6
Oi=gilbert+t=I-PER 6
t=I-PER+w=Agius 1
Oi=agius+t=I-PER 1
t=I-ORG+w=Attendance -4
Oi=attendance+t=I-ORG -4
t=O+w=Attendance 7
Oi=attendance+t=O 7
t=O+w=4-2 0
Oi=4-2+t=O 0
t=O+w=aggregate 1
Oi=aggregate+t=O 2
t=O+w=qualified 1
Oi=qualified+t=O 1
t=I-ORG+w=REUTER -1
Oi=reuter+t=I-ORG 2
t=I-PER+w=REUTER 4
Oi=reuter+t=I-PER 4
t=I-PER+w=HORSE -3
Oi=horse+t=I-PER -3
t=I-PER+w=RACING -4
Oi=racing+t=I-PER -4
t=I-MISC+w=PIVOTAL -1
Oi=pivotal+t=I-MISC -2
t=I-MISC+w=ENDS -1
Oi=ends+t=I-MISC -1
t=I-MISC+w=25-YEAR -1
Oi=25-year+t=I-MISC -1
t=I-MISC+w=WAIT -4
Oi=wait+t=I-MISC -4
t=I-PER+w=TRAINER -2
Oi=trainer+t=I-PER -5
t=O+w=PRESCOTT -3
Oi=prescott+t=O -4
t=O+w=HORSE 5
Oi=horse+t=O 5
t=O+w=RACING 6
Oi=racing+t=O 3
t=I-PER+w=PIVOTAL 2
Oi=pivotal+t=I-PER 7
t=O+w=ENDS 5
Oi=ends+t=O 5
t=O+w=25-YEAR 2
Oi=25-year+t=O 2
t=O+w=WAIT 9
Oi=wait+t=O 9
t=O+w=TRAINER 3
Oi=trainer+t=O 7
t=I-PER+w=PRESCOTT 3
Oi=prescott+t=I-PER 5
t=O+w=YORK -3
Oi=york+t=O -6
t=O+w=England -7
Oi=england+t=O -7
t=I-LOC+w=YORK 4
Oi=york+t=I-LOC 9
t=I-LOC+w=England 8
Oi=england+t=I-LOC 14
t=I-ORG+w=Sir -2
Oi=sir+t=I-ORG -2
t=I-ORG+w=Mark -2
Oi=mark+t=I-ORG -2
t=I-ORG+w=Prescott -1
Oi=prescott+t=I-ORG -1
t=O+w=landed 0
Oi=landed+t=O 0
t=O+w=victory 3
Oi=victory+t=O 4
t=O+w=25 0
Oi=25+t=O 0
t=O+w=trainer 0
t=O+w=sprinter 1
Oi=sprinter+t=O 1
t=O+w=Pivotal -3
Oi=pivotal+t=O -3
t=O+w=100-30 1
Oi=100-30+t=O 1
t=O+w=chance 2
Oi=chance+t=O 2
t=O+w=Nunthorpe -4
Oi=nunthorpe+t=O 2
t=O+w=Stakes -4
Oi=stakes+t=O 3
t=O+w=Sir 5
Oi=sir+t=O 5
t=I-PER+w=Prescott 2
t=I-PER+w=Pivotal 5
t=I-MISC+w=Nunthorpe 4
Oi=nunthorpe+t=I-MISC 2
t=I-MISC+w=Stakes 4
Oi=stakes+t=I-MISC 1
t=O+w=three-year-old 1
Oi=three-year-old+t=O 1
t=O+w=partnered 0
Oi=partnered+t=O 0
t=O+w=veteran 1
Oi=veteran+t=O 4
t=I-PER+w=George 4
Oi=george+t=I-PER 4
t=I-PER+w=Duffield 0
Oi=duffield+t=I-PER 0
t=O+w=snatched 0
Oi=snatched+t=O 0
t=O+w=short 1
t=I-PER+w=head -2
Oi=head+t=I-PER 5
t=I-PER+w=verdict -1
Oi=verdict+t=I-PER -1
t=I-PER+w=stride -1
Oi=stride+t=I-PER -1
t=O+w=deny 1
Oi=deny+t=O 1
t=I-PER+w=Eveningperformance 4
Oi=eveningperformance+t=I-PER 4
t=O+w=16-1 4
Oi=16-1+t=O 4
t=O+w=trained 0
Oi=trained+t=O 0
t=O+w=Henry -3
Oi=henry+t=O -3
t=I-PER+w=Candy 3
Oi=candy+t=I-PER 3
t=O+w=ridden 0
Oi=ridden+t=O 0
t=I-PER+w=Chris 4
Oi=chris+t=I-PER 4
t=I-PER+w=Rutter 0
Oi=rutter+t=I-PER 0
t=O+w=head 5
Oi=head+t=O -2
t=O+w=verdict 1
Oi=verdict+t=O 1
t=O+w=stride 1
Oi=stride+t=O 1
t=I-PER+w=Henry 5
Oi=henry+t=I-PER 5
t=I-PER+w=Hever 3
Oi=hever+t=I-PER 3
t=I-PER+w=Golf -1
Oi=golf+t=I-PER -2
t=O+w=11-4 4
Oi=11-4+t=O 4
t=I-PER+w=Prix -1
Oi=prix+t=I-PER -3
t=O+w=l -2
Oi=l+t=O 4
t=O+w=Abbaye -2
Oi=abbaye+t=O -2
t=O+w=winner 1
Oi=winner+t=O 5
t=O+w=Longchamp -1
Oi=longchamp+t=O -1
t=O+w=finished 0
Oi=finished+t=O 0
t=O+w=third 6
t=O+w=lengths 0
Oi=lengths+t=O 2
t=O+w=away 1
Oi=away+t=O 4
t=O+w=7-4 2
Oi=7-4+t=O 2
t=O+w=Mind -5
Oi=mind+t=O -3
t=I-LOC+w=Games -4
Oi=games+t=I-LOC -4
t=O+w=fourth 3
Oi=fourth+t=O 3
t=I-MISC+w=Prix 3
Oi=prix+t=I-MISC 7
t=I-MISC+w=de 2
Oi=de+t=I-MISC 1
t=I-MISC+w=l 2
Oi=l+t=I-MISC -1
t=I-MISC+w=' 1
Oi='+t=I-MISC 1
p=''+t=I-MISC 2
t=I-MISC+w=Abbaye 5
Oi=abbaye+t=I-MISC 5
t=I-LOC+w=Longchamp 3
Oi=longchamp+t=I-LOC 3
t=I-PER+w=Mind 8
Oi=mind+t=I-PER 6
t=I-PER+w=Games 2
Oi=games+t=I-PER 0
t=I-MISC+w=Pivotal -1
t=I-MISC+w=Royal -2
Oi=royal+t=I-MISC -2
t=I-MISC+w=Ascot -1
Oi=ascot+t=I-MISC -1
t=I-MISC+w=winner -1
Oi=winner+t=I-MISC -1
t=I-LOC+w=June -2
Oi=june+t=I-LOC -3
t=O+w=may 0
t=O+w=now 2
t=O+w=aimed 0
Oi=aimed+t=O 0
t=O+w=season 1
Oi=season+t=O 6
t=I-MISC+w=top -1
Oi=top+t=I-MISC -1
t=I-MISC+w=sprint -2
Oi=sprint+t=I-MISC -3
t=I-MISC+w=race -1
Oi=race+t=I-MISC -1
t=I-PER+w=Royal 1
Oi=royal+t=I-PER 1
t=I-PER+w=Ascot 3
Oi=ascot+t=I-PER 3
t=O+w=sprint 2
Oi=sprint+t=O 5
t=O+w=race 2
Oi=race+t=O 3
t=O+w=reluctant 1
Oi=reluctant+t=O 1
t=O+w=go 0
Oi=go+t=O 0
t=O+w=enclosure 0
Oi=enclosure+t=O 0
t=O+w=result 0
Oi=result+t=O 5
t=O+w=photo-finish 1
Oi=photo-finish+t=O 1
t=O+w=Twenty-five 0
Oi=twenty-five+t=O 0
t=O+w=never 1
Oi=never+t=O 1
t=O+w=so 1
Oi=so+t=O 1
t=O+w=thought 1
Oi=thought+t=O 1
t=O+w=better 2
Oi=better+t=O 2
t=O+w=wait 0
t=O+w=bit 1
Oi=bit+t=O 1
t=O+w=longer 1
Oi=longer+t=O 1
t=O+w=sad 1
Oi=sad+t=O 1
t=O+w=Candy -2
Oi=candy+t=O -2
t=O+w=am -1
Oi=am+t=O -1
t=O+w=godfather 1
Oi=godfather+t=O 1
t=O+w=daughter 1
Oi=daughter+t=O 1
t=O+w=Like 0
t=I-PER+w=Jack 4
Oi=jack+t=I-PER 4
t=I-PER+w=Berry 2
Oi=berry+t=I-PER 2
t=O+w=gone 0
Oi=gone+t=O 0
t=O+w=search 1
Oi=search+t=O 1
t=O+w=success 1
Oi=success+t=O 1
t=O+w=around 1
Oi=around+t=O 1
t=O+w=profession 0
Oi=profession+t=O 0
t=O+w=I`m 1
Oi=i`m+t=O 1
t=O+w=disappointed 0
Oi=disappointed+t=O 0
t=O+w=feel 1
Oi=feel+t=O 1
t=O+w=suicidal 1
Oi=suicidal+t=O 1
t=O+w=well 1
t=O+w=furlongs 0
Oi=furlongs+t=O 0
t=O+w=metres 0
Oi=metres+t=O 4
t=O+w=just 2
Oi=just+t=O 2
t=O+w=quicken 0
Oi=quicken+t=O 0
t=I-PER+w=NUNTHORPE -3
Oi=nunthorpe+t=I-PER -3
t=I-PER+w=STAKES -3
Oi=stakes+t=I-PER -3
t=O+w=RESULTS 8
t=O+w=NUNTHORPE 6
t=O+w=STAKES 6
t=O+w=Result 0
t=O+w=two-year-olds 0
Oi=two-year-olds+t=O 0
t=O+w=upwards 0
Oi=upwards+t=O 0
t=O+w=run 2
Oi=run+t=O 4
t=O+w=five 3
Oi=five+t=O -1
t=O+w=km 0
Oi=km+t=O 4
t=O+w=1. 1
Oi=1.+t=O 1
t=I-LOC+w=Pivotal -1
Oi=pivotal+t=I-LOC -1
t=O+w=2. 8
Oi=2.+t=O 8
t=O+w=Eveningperformance -4
Oi=eveningperformance+t=O -4
t=I-PER+w=16-1 -4
Oi=16-1+t=I-PER -4
t=I-MISC+w=3. -3
Oi=3.+t=I-MISC -3
t=I-MISC+w=Hever -3
Oi=hever+t=I-MISC -3
t=I-MISC+w=Rose -2
Oi=rose+t=I-MISC -2
t=I-MISC+w=11-4 -1
Oi=11-4+t=I-MISC -1
t=I-PER+w=Jason 3
Oi=jason+t=I-PER 3
t=I-PER+w=Weaver 4
Oi=weaver+t=I-PER 6
t=O+w=3. 9
Oi=3.+t=O 9
t=O+w=Eight 0
Oi=eight+t=O 2
t=O+w=ran 0
Oi=ran+t=O 0
t=O+w=Favourite 1
t=O+w=4th 1
Oi=4th+t=O 1
t=O+w=Distances 0
Oi=distances+t=O 0
t=O+w=1-1/4 0
Oi=1-1/4+t=O 0
t=O+w=Winner 3
t=O+w=owned 0
Oi=owned+t=O 0
t=I-PER+w=Cheveley -1
Oi=cheveley+t=I-PER -1
t=I-PER+w=Park -2
Oi=park+t=I-PER -2
t=I-PER+w=Stud -1
Oi=stud+t=I-PER -1
t=I-PER+w=Sir -3
Oi=sir+t=I-PER -3
t=I-ORG+w=Cheveley 3
Oi=cheveley+t=I-ORG 3
t=I-ORG+w=Park 0
Oi=park+t=I-ORG 0
t=I-ORG+w=Stud 3
Oi=stud+t=I-ORG 3
t=O+w=Mark -2
Oi=mark+t=O 0
t=O+w=Prescott -1
t=O+w=Newmarket -2
Oi=newmarket+t=O -2
t=I-LOC+w=Newmarket 4
Oi=newmarket+t=I-LOC 4
t=O+w=Value 4
t=O+w=72,464 0
Oi=72,464+t=O 0
t=O+w=sterling 1
Oi=sterling+t=O 5
t=O+w=112,200 0
Oi=112,200+t=O 0
t=O+w=TENNIS 4
Oi=tennis+t=O 3
t=I-PER+w=RESULTS -4
Oi=results+t=I-PER -4
t=I-PER+w=AT -4
Oi=at+t=I-PER -4
t=I-PER+w=TOSHIBA -2
Oi=toshiba+t=I-PER -3
t=I-PER+w=CLASSIC -2
Oi=classic+t=I-PER -3
t=I-MISC+w=TOSHIBA 3
Oi=toshiba+t=I-MISC 6
t=I-MISC+w=CLASSIC 3
Oi=classic+t=I-MISC 9
t=I-LOC+w=CARLSBAD 4
Oi=carlsbad+t=I-LOC 4
t=I-ORG+w=California 1
Oi=california+t=I-ORG 2
t=I-ORG+w=1996-08-21 -2
Oi=1996-08-21+t=I-ORG -2
t=I-LOC+w=California 5
Oi=california+t=I-LOC 5
t=O+w=1996-08-21 7
Oi=1996-08-21+t=O 7
t=O+w=Results 1
t=O+w=450,000 1
Oi=450,000+t=O 1
t=O+w=Toshiba -1
Oi=toshiba+t=O -1
t=I-LOC+w=Classic -1
Oi=classic+t=I-LOC -1
t=O+w=tennis 1
t=O+w=tournament 3
Oi=tournament+t=O 3
t=I-MISC+w=Toshiba 3
t=I-MISC+w=Classic 6
t=O+w=prefix 2
Oi=prefix+t=O 2
t=O+w=denotes 1
Oi=denotes+t=O 1
t=O+w=seeding 2
Oi=seeding+t=O 2
t=O+w=Second 2
t=I-LOC+w=Arantxa -1
Oi=arantxa+t=I-LOC -1
t=O+w=Sanchez -1
Oi=sanchez+t=O -1
t=I-LOC+w=Vicario -1
Oi=vicario+t=I-LOC -1
t=I-LOC+w=Spain 6
Oi=spain+t=I-LOC 6
t=O+w=Naoko -1
Oi=naoko+t=O -1
t=I-LOC+w=Kijimuta -1
Oi=kijimuta+t=I-LOC -1
t=I-PER+w=Arantxa 2
Oi=arantxa+t=I-PER 2
t=I-PER+w=Sanchez 5
Oi=sanchez+t=I-PER 5
t=I-PER+w=Vicario 2
Oi=vicario+t=I-PER 2
t=I-PER+w=Naoko 1
Oi=naoko+t=I-PER 1
t=I-PER+w=Kijimuta 1
Oi=kijimuta+t=I-PER 1
t=O+w=1-6 0
Oi=1-6+t=O 0
t=O+w=6-4 0
Oi=6-4+t=O 0
t=O+w=6-3 4
Oi=6-3+t=O 4
t=O+w=4 2
Oi=4+t=O 2
t=I-PER+w=Kimiko 3
Oi=kimiko+t=I-PER 3
t=I-PER+w=Date 5
Oi=date+t=I-PER 1
t=I-PER+w=Japan -3
Oi=japan+t=I-PER -3
t=I-PER+w=Yone 1
Oi=yone+t=I-PER 1
t=I-PER+w=Kamio 1
Oi=kamio+t=I-PER 1
t=O+w=6-2 1
Oi=6-2+t=O 1
t=O+w=7-5 0
Oi=7-5+t=O 0
t=I-PER+w=Sandrine 1
Oi=sandrine+t=I-PER 1
t=I-PER+w=Testud 1
Oi=testud+t=I-PER 1
t=O+w=7 0
Oi=7+t=O 0
t=I-LOC+w=Sugiyama -1
Oi=sugiyama+t=I-LOC -1
t=O+w=4-6 1
Oi=4-6+t=O 1
t=I-PER+w=Ai 3
Oi=ai+t=I-PER 3
t=I-PER+w=Sugiyama 3
Oi=sugiyama+t=I-PER 3
t=O+w=8 1
Oi=8+t=O 1
t=I-PER+w=Nathalie 2
Oi=nathalie+t=I-PER 2
t=I-PER+w=Tauziat 3
Oi=tauziat+t=I-PER 3
t=I-PER+w=Shi-Ting 0
Oi=shi-ting+t=I-PER 0
t=I-PER+w=Wang 2
Oi=wang+t=I-PER 2
t=I-PER+w=HAMLET -1
Oi=hamlet+t=I-PER -2
t=I-PER+w=CUP -5
Oi=cup+t=I-PER -7
t=I-MISC+w=HAMLET 2
Oi=hamlet+t=I-MISC 3
t=I-MISC+w=CUP 8
t=I-MISC+w=COMMACK -1
Oi=commack+t=I-MISC -1
t=I-MISC+w=New 4
t=I-MISC+w=York -4
Oi=york+t=I-MISC -4
t=I-MISC+w=1996-08-21 -1
Oi=1996-08-21+t=I-MISC -1
t=I-LOC+w=COMMACK 4
Oi=commack+t=I-LOC 4
t=I-LOC+w=New 0
t=I-LOC+w=York 5
t=I-LOC+w=Waldbaum -1
Oi=waldbaum+t=I-LOC -1
t=O+w=Hamlet 3
Oi=hamlet+t=O 2
t=I-MISC+w=Waldbaum 4
